<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Fidelity Lowers Value of Stake in Musk’s X by 5.7% in February</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400665862&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Fidelity’s Blue Chip Growth Fund cut the value of its position in X by 5.7% in February, implying a 73% decline in the former Twitter Inc. since Elon Musk bought the social-media company.
Fidelity, which gained a stake in X by helping Musk complete his $44 billion purchase in October ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Stournaras Says Four 2024 Rate Cuts Possible</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400658667&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Yannis Stournaras said a total of four interest rate cuts is feasible in 2024, for a reduction of 100 basis points by year-end. 
“If inflation develops in line with our March forecast and if this trend continues until the end of the year,...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Holzmann Won’t Seek Second Term as Austrian Central Bank Governor</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400645375&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Robert Holzmann said he won’t seek a second term as head of the Austrian National Bank when his stint ends in August 2025.  
“It was clear to me five years ago that this is a job for six years and that I won’t seek a second term thereafte...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>