<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>UBS Drops Long-Held Bearish View on India, Downgrades Hong Kong</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12464565800828088308</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG is abandoning its long-held bearish view on Indian stocks, upgrading the market to neutral from underweight as it realigns its strategy given global trade uncertainties. 
The brokerage is becoming more optimistic on the South Asian market amid a growing preference for def...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>JP Morgan Chase legt solides erstes Quartal vor</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7001546100188060085</link>
<author>Börsen-Kurier</author>
<description>Red. JP Morgan Chase (ISIN: US46625H1 005) legte vergangene Woche die Ergebnisse für das erste Quartal 2025 vor. Der Nettogewinn zog um 9 % auf 14,6 MrdUSD (12,84 Mrd€) an und übertraf damit die Prognosen von 13,2 MrdUSD (11,61 Mrd€) deutlich. Während der Zinsertrag um 1 % zulegte, entwickelten sich...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>»Wir erschaffen eine neue Spezies«</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=546219445367182663</link>
<author>DIE ZEIT</author>
<description>DIE ZEIT: Herr Tegmark, wenn wir künstliche Intelligenz nicht regulieren, wird sie die Menschheit wahrscheinlich auslöschen – sagen Sie. Warum ist die KI so viel gefährlicher als andere Technologien?
Max Tegmark: Es ist die einzige Technik, die selbst neue Technik entwickeln könnte. KI wird uns künf...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Goldminenfonds schlagen andere Anlagen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6633411216652293166</link>
<author>Handelsblatt</author>
<description>Fonds von Goldminenprodukten haben so gut abgeschlossen wie keine andere große Anlageklasse. Anleger sollten jedoch eines beachten.

Fonds auf Gold- und Edelmetallaktien haben im ersten Quartal 2025 andere wichtige Anlagestrategien weit hinter sich gelassen. Während viele internationale Aktienindize...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>So legen Sie 5 Millionen Euro richtig an</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17340568494216097629</link>
<author>Capital+</author>
<description>Mehr Vermögen macht die Geldanlage nicht leichter, sondern komplizierter. So behalten Sie selbst bei einer Summe von 5 Millionen Euro den Überblick

Wenn Sie 5 Millionen Euro anlegen können, gehören Sie zu den obersten 0,1 Prozent in Deutschland. In der Regel bewegt man sich hier dann schon in profe...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Knot Says Neutral Is Right Policy Setting as Shocks Unfold</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3983190353255511619</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Klaas Knot said he doesn’t see a need to stimulate the economy with lower interest rates as the medium-term impacts of recent economic shocks remain unclear.
While inflation may slow more rapidly than previously anticipated, the fallout f...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS China Fund Says Shun EV Stocks for ‘Haven’ Consumer Staples</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16976023716221299522</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A top-performing Chinese equities veteran is betting on consumer stocks with haven characteristics to outperform amid ongoing tariff conflicts.
Bin Shi, head of China equities at UBS Asset Management, is avoiding crowded names that have rallied significantly this year. He prefers to o...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Predicts Wage Growth Will Slow Sharply at End of This Year</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5228641932056450112</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
The European Central Bank’s main gauge of future pay growth continued to indicate a sharp slowdown in 2025, underpinning expectations for a further retreat in inflation that may allow more interest-rate cuts.
The ECB’s wag...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Villeroy Sees No Inflation Risk, Says Further Rate Cuts Likely</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13403013417499018452</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank will probably lower interest rates further this year as there are currently no inflation risks, according to Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau.
The effect of President Donald Trump’s tariffs on euro-zone prices is uncertain and could on the...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Cuts Dollar Outlook Again, Says US-China Is Key for Its Path</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6251580076603663483</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A unit of UBS Group AG cut its dollar forecast for the second time in under two months citing that the greenback’s performance hinges on the outcome of the US-China trade face-off.
UBS Investment Bank’s Shahab Jalinoos, Alvise Marino and Vassili Serebriakov said the impact of Presiden...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Rates May Have to Fall Below Neutral on Trade, Muller Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6030455340535105772</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank may have to lower interest rates to levels that stimulate the economy if trade uncertainty proves more damaging for growth, according to European Central Bank Governing Council member Madis Muller.
Borrowing costs have already reached levels that no longer re...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Head of iShares Canada Departs Firm</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7230141354243440204</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc.’s head of iShares in Canada, Helen Hayes, has left the firm as part of a broader restructuring, according to an internal memo seen by Bloomberg.
Hayes “expressed her intention to pursue new opportunities outside of the firm,” said the memo, which outlined a series of or...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS, General Atlantic Discuss Private Credit Partnership</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3218329747304832947</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG is in advanced talks with alternative-asset manager General Atlantic to push into the $1.6 trillion private credit market through a strategic partnership, according to people familiar with the matter. 
The two firms are working toward a cooperation agreement that could be...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Finanzberatung per KI: Wer steht für Fehler gerade?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3836780114697023076</link>
<author>Spiegel.de</author>
<description>Max Bachem hat das Fintech Xaver gegründet, das eine KI-Finanzberatung entwickelt. Die Kölner Firma gilt als heiße Investorenwette. Im Podcast spricht der Unternehmer darüber, ob KI gute Investments tätigen kann – und wer bei Fehlern die Verantwortung trägt.

Für sein Produkt braucht Max Bachem , 38...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>So schützen Sie Ihr Vermögen im Kriegsfall</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16809077340081374888</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Seit Russlands Überfall auf die Ukraine ist der Krieg zurück in Europa. Wie können Anleger zumindest ihr Vermögen für den Fall einer Ausweitung des Konflikts absichern?

Erstveröffentlichung: 2025-04-23 14:09:00 letzte Aktualisierung: 2025-04-23 14:31:03
WiWo Coachist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bundesbank will Bargeld erhalten und fördern</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=742257073323388618</link>
<author>FAZ.NET</author>
<description>Mit großer Mehrheit sprechen sich die Menschen in Deutschland für den Erhalt des Bargelds aus. Trotz mancher Nachteile will auch die Bundesbank die Scheine noch lange Zeit im Umlauf halten.

Ein Zukunft ohne Bargeld mögen sich die meisten Menschen in Deutschland nicht vorstellen. Laut einer Umfrage ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Schlimmer als die Finanzkrise 2008: Warum Milliardär Ray Dalio jetzt Alarm schlägt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5544598196285960366</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Star-Investor und Milliardär Ray Dalio warnt vor weit mehr als nur einer Rezession. Eine explosive Mischung aus Schulden, Zöllen und geopolitischen Spannungen bringt das Weltfinanzsystem ins Wanken – und Anleger müssen sich auf dramatische Veränderungen einstellen.
Zölle, Schulden, Systemkrise: Währ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>