<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB Plans to Clamp Down on Banks Ignoring Its Demands for Fixes</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451869954&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is set to crack down on lenders that are slow to deal with fixes the supervisor demands of them, after growing frustrated with a perceived lack of responsiveness.
The ECB has issued more than 5,000 supervisory measures a year on average since it started overs...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Very Close to Meeting 2% Inflation Target, Lagarde Tells FT</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451841590&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is nearing its consumer-price target but must remain alert to lingering dangers in some sectors, according to President Christine Lagarde.
“We’re getting very close to that stage when we can declare that we have sustainably brought inflation to our medium-ter...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nach gut einem Jahr: Immac Klinik-Fonds voll platziert</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451844639&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Cash.Online</author>
<description>Der Fonds investiert in die „Klinik im Kurpark“ in Bad Rothenfelde, Niedersachsen, eine auf Vorsorge, Rehabilitation und Anschlussheilbehandlungen spezialisierte Einrichtung mit 299 stationären Betten. Betreiberin der Klinik ist die zur Hasselmann Gruppe gehörende Klinik im Kurpark GmbH.
Immac hatte...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nur gut 20 Fusionen trotz Problemen bei Volksbanken</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451878762&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Erstveröffentlichung: 2024-12-23 18:01:19 letzte Aktualisierung: 2024-12-23 18:01:19
Angesichts der Skandalserie bei mehreren Volksbanken war 2024 für die deutschen Genossenschaftsbanken ein schwieriges Jahr. Und doch gab es vergleichsweise wenig Zusammenschlüsse im Sektor der Volks- und Raiffeisenb...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Arkema : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451842115&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Arkema : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,01% du capital et 4,02% des droits de vote (17/12/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Société Générale : BlackRock, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451842113&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Société Générale : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,62% du capital et 5,08% des droits de vote (20/12/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>