<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Indonesian Bonds Seen Extending Rally on Rate-Cut Expectations</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17155368968249934369</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Indonesian bonds have room to rally further, according to strategists, on expectations of further interest-rate cuts by the central bank.
Nomura Holdings Inc. says the benchmark 10-year yield may slide to 5.75% by year-end from the current 6%. PT Sucor Sekuritas sees it falling to as ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB to Stay on Hold Before Year-End Forecasts: Decision Guide</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16277640301877923111</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is set to keep interest rates unchanged for a third meeting, awaiting year-end projections that will offer greater clarity on harm caused by trade tensions and France’s fiscal crisis.
The deposit rate will be held at 2% on Thursday, according to all responden...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gold Rises as Fed Divisions Raise Questions Over Rate Outlook</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13869478303962234695</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Gold staged a partial recovery following a run of losses as traders weighed conflicting views from Federal Reserve policymakers about the chance of more rate cuts.
Bullion rose as much as 0.9% to trade near $3,967 an ounce after falling almost 5% over the previous four sessions. Fed C...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Revival des grünen Gases</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17297953899945304620</link>
<author>Börse Online</author>
<description>Wenn von Megatrends an der Börse die Rede ist, fallen meist Schlagworte wie künstliche Intelligenz oder Digitalisierung. Ein Thema, das immer wieder mal gehypt wurde, dann vom Radar verschwand und nun am Kapitalmarkt wieder aufploppt, ist Wasserstoff. Die Aktienmärkte reagieren momentan mit einer Mi...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>