<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Huawei EV Partner Seres Seeks $1.7 Billion in HK Listing</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15219257506382133495</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Seres Group Co. started taking investor orders for a Hong Kong listing that may raise as much as HK$13.2 billion ($1.7 billion), making the electric-vehicle maker the latest big Chinese company to go public in the financial hub.
The Chongqing-based company is offering 100 million shar...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>South Korea's Housing Market Is a `Ticking Bomb,' President Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6363105055963709358</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- South Korean President Lee Jae Myung warned that the country’s property market is a bubble on the point of bursting, as he backed the Bank of Korea’s decision to hold rates last week.
Amid concerns that cheaper borrowing may further fuel the rally in property prices, Lee said it was i...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>«Rationaler Überschwang» bei KI</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17662904430624934606</link>
<author>Neue Zürcher Zeitung</author>
<description>Acht Billionen, also 8000 Milliarden Dollar, soll der US-Chip-Hersteller Nvidia in einem Jahr wert sein – das ist fast doppelt so viel wie heute. Das glaubt ein Technologie-Analyst der britischen Grossbank HSBC. Die Zahl ist eine Mutmassung, wie vieles, wenn es um künstliche Intelligenz (KI) geht. D...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stehaufmännchen Börse</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17471086476668228689</link>
<author>FOCUS online</author>
<description>Stehaufmännchen-Zeit an der Börse: Weiterhin werden Rückschläge schnell weggeatmet. Waren es vor einigen Wochen neue Zolldrohungen aus den USA Richtung China, so hatte in der Vorwoche die Nachricht von Kreditproblemen bei US-Regionalbanken den Börsianern spürbare Kursrücksetzer eingebracht. Diese wu...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>