<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Barrick Mining: Die Aktie könnte jetzt nach oben ausbrechen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5096862540586340332</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Georg Pröbstl
Ende Juli hatte ich an dieser Stelle Barrick Mining risikofreudigen Anleger zum Kauf empfohlen mit der Chance auf schnelle Kursgewinne. Denn die Aktie des Goldproduzenten hatte damals wichtige Hürden im Chart erreicht. Die Wahrscheinlichkeit schien hoch, dass der Kurs des Minenunterneh...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>15 Dax-Konzerne verbuchen trotz Krise Rekordgewinne – wie ist das möglich?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2270751438627107391</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Mit voraussichtlich 115 Milliarden Euro dürften die 40 Dax-Konzerne in diesem Jahr ihren dritthöchsten Nettogewinn in der deutschen Wirtschaftsgeschichte einfahren. Das zeigen die bereits präsentierten Halbjahresbilanzen, die Erwartungen der Unternehmen an das zweite Halbjahr, die daraus abgeleitete...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazimir Urges Vigilance on Upside Risks to Inflation</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11547053047494297077</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank must remain on alert to tackle upside dangers to inflation, according to Governing Council member Peter Kazimir.
While the ECB has brought rates into a “comfortable, neutral territory,” it must stay nimble in an increasingly volatile global environment, the S...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kocher Says Euro-Area Inflation Risks ‘Quite Balanced’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13636361041676297372</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Martin Kocher said officials stand ready to react to changes in the economic data even if inflation risks for the region are “quite balanced” at the moment. 
“Personally, I think they are quite balanced in terms of upward and downward pot...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Warner Bros.’ Win for Fallen Angel Debt: Credit Weekly</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13548123638461102293</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Warner Bros. Discovery Inc.’s junk bonds surged this week, handing big gains to investors that bet on the company when its future looked comparatively bleak. More such opportunities may be coming, according to money managers including Loomis Sayles & Co.   
The entertainment company’s...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Schnabel Backs Steady Rates Amid Upside Inflation Risks</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=907039705464685491</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should maintain its current level of interest rates, with dangers to prices tilted to the upside, according to Executive Board member Isabel Schnabel. 
In a presentation for an event Monday in Luxembourg, Schnabel said small deviations from the 2% inflation t...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Flips $3 Billion of Rieder’s Mutual Funds Into ETFs</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17069108201816533525</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. is converting two mutual funds — managed by Chief Investment Officer of global fixed income Rick Rieder — into ETFs to better fit the strategies into the firm’s booming model-portfolio ecosystem.
The actively managed mutual funds will become the iShares Dynamic Equity A...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Der Mensch bleibt im Mittelpunkt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12099633207421012558</link>
<author>Kronen Zeitung</author>
<description>Frau Generaldirektorin, wie bewerten Sie generell das Potenzial von Künstlicher Intelligenz für die Finanzbranche-insbesondere für Regionalbanken wie die Sparkasse OÖ?
Künstliche Intelligenz hat das Potenzial, die Finanzbranche grundlegend zu verändern. Ich sehe KI nicht nur als technologischen Fort...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrefour : J.P. Morgan [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16486066226780289673</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Carrefour : J.P. Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient, indirectement par l'intermédiaire des sociétés qu'elle contrÎle, 5,81% du capital et 4,81% des droits de vote (11/09/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Eiffage : BlackRock, agissant[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7355768351156778105</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Eiffage : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 6,03% du capital et 4,91% des droits de vote (12/09/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abivax J.P. Morgan Chase [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10789463935074337345</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Abivax J.P. Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient, indirectement par l'intermédiaire des sociétés J.P. Morgan Prime Inc., J.P. Morgan Securities plc et J.P. Morgan Securities LLC qu'elle contrÎle, 5,35% du capital et 4,76% des droits de vot...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ubisfot Entertainment : BlackRock,[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8087081088070634653</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Ubisfot Entertainment : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,22% du capital et 4,72% des droits de vote (12/09/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Valeo : BlackRock, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3681061882260948863</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Valeo : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,61% du capital et 4,99% des droits de vote (26/08/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Accor : BlackRock, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=702953241103066505</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse le seuil de 5% du capital et détient, pour le compte desdits clients et fonds, 5,18% du capital et 4,45% des droits de vote (11/09/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Thales : BlackRock, agissant[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14602413335303252421</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Thales : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 4,97% du capital et 3,39% des droits de vote (28/08/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrefour : J.P. Morgan [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4134527930713698189</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Carrefour : J.P. Morgan Securities a franchi indirectement en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 4,93% du capital et 4,08% des droits de vote (18/08/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vallourec : Fidelity [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11089253076209461075</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Vallourec : Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company llc a franchi individuellement en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient individuellement 4,98% du capital et 5,07% des droits de vote (11/09/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Inventiva : J.P. Morgan[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5504877231326210718</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Inventiva : J.P. Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient, indirectement par l'intermédiaire des sociétés J.P. Morgan Prime Inc., J.P. Morgan Securities plc et J.P. Morgan Securities llc qu'elle contrÎle, 2,33% du capital...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>AXA : BlackRock, agissant[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15056274723711469814</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>AXA : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 6,07% du capital et 5,04% des droits de vote (18/08/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>