<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Plans to Hire 1,200 People for Ramp-Up in India</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459772295&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. plans to hire nearly 1,200 people to expand two support hubs in India and build out its artificial intelligence capabilities in the country, according to people familiar with the matter.
The world’s largest asset manager is hiring for its iHubs, as the centers are known...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB May Need to Cut Rates Below Neutral Level, Centeno Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459658368&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank may need to cut interest rates below neutral levels to stimulate economic growth, Governing Council member Mario Centeno told Reuters in an interview.
- “We need to keep the trajectory of interest rates going down,” he says
- ECB’s key rate needs to reach 2% ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vanguard’s Record Fee Cut Puts Rivals BlackRock, Invesco in Tough Spot</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459640683&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Vanguard Group Inc.’s biggest salvo yet in its campaign to cut fees for the investing masses presents industry rivals with a painful choice. Follow suit and lose potentially hundreds of millions in revenue — or hold the line and risk losing badly needed market share.
The Valley Forge,...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock to List Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Product in Europe</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459640662&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc., the world’s largest asset manager, is preparing to list an exchange-traded product tied directly to Bitcoin in Europe, following on from the success of its $58 billion US ETF tracking the cryptocurrency.
The fund will likely be domiciled in Switzerland, according to pe...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Lane Says Agility Needed on Rates Amid Inflation Risks</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459634307&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should remain agile in setting monetary policy since inflation risks remain in both directions, according to Chief Economist Philip Lane.
While officials are confident that consumer-price gains will settle at 2% this year, Lane flagged that getting to this po...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Switzerland’s Finma Pushes Back Against Calls to Protect UBS</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459623525&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Switzerland’s financial watchdog signaled it’s opposed to giving UBS Group AG any special treatment to aid its competitiveness against global rivals, as the country undergoes a regulatory overhaul following the collapse of Credit Suisse.
With the Swiss government likely to substantial...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Wage Tracker Points to Steep Slowdown This Year</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459614874&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank’s main gauge of future euro-zone pay growth continued to signal a sharp slowdown in 2025, underpinning hopes for a further retreat in inflation that should allow more interest-rate cuts.
The ECB’s wage tracker, published Wednesday, predicts salaries rising by...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Corum-Immo-Fonds: Entwicklung gegen den Trend</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459416269&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Kurier</author>
<description>Im Gegensatz zu den meisten Immo-Fonds schlossen die Corum-Produkte 2024 mit ansehnlichen Renditen ab.
Patrick Baldia. Mit den Zinserhöhungen ab 2022 verloren bekanntlich viele Immobilienveranlagungen an Attraktivität. Zu den größten Verlierern gehören neben Aktien offene Immobilienfonds. Nachdem di...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>„Da frag ich erstmal ChatGPT“</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2459423878&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Cash.</author>
<description>Zugegeben, die Frage ist ziemlich eindimensional: „Welches ist die beste Lebensversicherung in Deutschland?“ Und doch wird sie vermutlich so oder ähnlich jeden Tag von Kunden an ihr jeweils bevorzugtes KI-Programm gestellt werden – bezogen auf Versicherungen aller Art, andere Finanzprodukte oder Unt...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>