<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>HSBC Looking to Join AI Infrastructure Finance Boom, Keefe Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434267549&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- HSBC Holdings Plc wants to join in the rush to finance the infrastructure needed to roll out artificial intelligence, according to one of the lender’s most senior investment bankers.
“We’re actually ramping up our presence in infrastructure finance,” Gerry Keefe, co-head of global ban...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>EU Bank Profitability Hit Record Just as ECB Started Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434267538&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The profitability of Europe’s top banks hit a record high just as the European Central Bank cut interest rates for the first time in almost five years.
Aggregate return on equity for the 110 lenders directly supervised by the ECB hit 10.11% in the second quarter, data published by the...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro Zone’s Teetering Economy Fuels Bets on Faster ECB Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434259789&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A shock decline in the euro zone’s main survey of the private sector economy just gave the European Central Bank a reason to speed up interest-rate cuts — at least in the eyes of investors.
Whether that means another reduction next month is unclear — markets assign a 40% chance to suc...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Sees Marks & Spencer Hitting 2015 High on Market-Share Gains</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434259777&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Marks & Spencer Group Plc’s soaring shares are set to hit highs not seen in almost nine years as the UK retailer wins more customers for its food and clothing, according to analysts at UBS Group AG.
Yashraj Rajani and Sreedhar Mahamkali of UBS set a 12-month price target for M&S share...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>German Yield Curve Normalizes Amid Bets on Faster ECB Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434241280&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A key segment of the German yield curve has normalized as traders bet the European Central Bank will need to accelerate the pace of interest-rate cuts amid growing concern the region’s economic recovery has run out of steam.
The rate on two-year bunds fell below the 10-year equivalent...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>European Banks Are Factoring Climate Risks Into Loans, ECB Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434241268&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European banks are factoring climate risks into the terms of mortgages they grant, although they don’t fully grasp the potential costs, according to their top regulator.
The European Central Bank found that loans secured by real estate in “high climate risk areas” were more expensive ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BNP Paribas Agrees to Buy HSBC Unit in German Wealth Push</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434236596&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BNP Paribas SA agreed to buy HSBC Holdings Plc private banking operations in Germany, as the French lender seeks a bigger slice of the nation’s growing market for wealth management. 
Adding the unit will take assets under management in BNP Paribas’ local wealth management business to ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Says Services Prices Bigger Worry Than Slow Growth</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434236592&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank Governing Council member Martins Kazaks said the danger of persistent services inflation currently outweighs his concerns over the economy.
“In my opinion, the risk of service price inflation is still more significant at the moment, but as we move forward ste...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Deal Showcases Rise of Saudi Wealth Fund’s New Star</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434229358&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- When BlackRock Inc. landed a $5 billion investment pledge from Riyadh in April, pictured smiling alongside Larry Fink and Public Investment Fund Governor Yasir Al Rumayyan was an executive seen as a rising force within the sovereign investor.
That man, Yazeed Al Humied, is one of the ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deka finanziert wieder Flugzeuge, hält Immo-Exposure aufrecht</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434236152&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (German)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Die DekaBank findet nach einem zwischenzeitlichen Stopp des Neugeschäfts wieder Gefallen an der Flugzeugfinanzierung. Das hat Risikochefin Birgit Dietl-Benzin im Interview mit Bloomberg angedeutet. Mit dieser Strategie unterscheidet sich die DekaBank ebenso von Teilen der Konkurrenz w...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>