<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Near Deal to Buy HPS for Close to $12 Billion, FT Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446966790&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. is close to an agreement to buy private credit group HPS Investment Partners, as the world’s largest asset manager tries to compete in the fast-growing alternatives space, the Financial Times reported. 
The two sides have agreed on the broad outline of the deal with a g...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Credit Suisse Cocaine Case Overturned With UBS Acquittal</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446821337&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Credit Suisse’s 2022 conviction for failing to prevent the money laundering of a cocaine dealer’s profits was overturned by a Swiss appeals court following the death of one of its former employees who was found guilty in the case. 
A., as the former banker can only be named, died in A...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock, Vanguard Accused of Antitrust Violations by Texas</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446821331&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc., Vanguard Group Inc. and State Street Corp. were sued by a group of states led by Texas for allegedly breaking antitrust law by boosting electricity prices through their investments, in the highest-profile lawsuit yet against the beleaguered ESG industry.
Texas Attorney...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Cuts Four Loan Bankers in Hong Kong, Singapore as Deal Flow Slows</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446813019&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG cut four loan syndication bankers in Asia, according to people familiar with the matter, as elevated funding costs cast a pall over the market. 
The individuals, who joined as part of the 2023 takeover of Credit Suisse, left on Monday, said the people, who asked not to be...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BNP Wins Bid to Throw Out Broker’s Move to Claim Bigger Payout</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446813018&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BNP Paribas SA won a bid to throw out an attempt by a broker to claim a bigger payout following her historic £2 million ($2.5 million) equal pay case.
Stacey Macken, a prime brokerage manager, attempted to argue that her award should be boosted for inflation and pay rises, saying that...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Schnabel Sees Only Limited Room for Further Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446804656&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank needs to be wary of cutting interest rates too far as borrowing costs are already near a level that no longer restrains the economy and going lower could backfire, according to Executive Board member Isabel Schnabel.
Officials can continue to loosen monetary ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bis zu 50% bis nächstes Jahr: JP Morgan verrät die 2 besten Aktien, die Sie jetzt kaufen sollten</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446797644&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Sind das die zwei genialsten Aktienideen für das kommende Jahr? Die Analysten von JP Morgan haben zwei ihrer Top-Picks für 2025 enthüllt – mit einer Kurschance von bis zu 70 Prozent.
Neues Jahr, neues Glück: Das Jahr 2024 neigt sich dem Ende zu, und für Anleger könnte dies ein Grund zur Freude sein....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Große Fische im Datenmeer</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446589731&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Kurier</author>
<description>Warum KI im Gesundheitssektor die Großen bevorzugt. Ein Gastkommentar.
Red. Artificial Intelligence transformiert die Gesundheitsbranche - doch profitieren davon vorerst vor allem die Mega Caps. Sie haben die Ressourcen, die Daten und das Know-how, um aus dieser technologischen Revolution die größte...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>DKM 2024: Cash. verleiht Innovations-Awards</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446821327&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Cash.</author>
<description>„Unser Ziel ist, die Versicherbarkeit für Menschen mit leichten psychischen Beeinträchtigungen zu verbessern“
Mit ihrer neuen „Psyche-Klausel Berufsunfähigkeit“ will die Alte Leipziger Lebensversicherung Kunden mit psychischen Vorbelastungen eine Brücke zu einer BU-Absicherung bauen. Dafür erhält de...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>„Es ist wichtiger denn je, sich mit der Altersvorsorge auseinanderzusetzen“</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2446821351&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Cash.</author>
<description>Rentenpaket II, die Reform der privaten Altersvorsorge, die zweite Reform des Betriebsrentenstärkungsgesetzes. Aktuell ist bei Thema Altersvorsorge einiges in Bewegung. Auch weil die Regierung erkannt hat, dass die gesetzliche Rente allein für ein auskömmliches Leben im Alter kaum reichen dürfte. 1....</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>