<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Vanguard Taps Ex-Fidelity Executive to Lead New Wealth Division</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449192630&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Vanguard Group created a new advice and wealth management division and hired an outsider from Fidelity Investments to run it. 
Joanna Rotenberg, who was most recently president at Fidelity’s personal investing unit, will join Vanguard in January to lead the new business, the firm said...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Citi Says It’s Time to Bet Against Rapid ECB Interest-Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449148335&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Traders should wager on a slower pace of interest-rate cuts by the European Central Bank next year, according to Citigroup Inc., which says the market has gone overboard in betting on swift reductions.
Money markets currently expect the ECB to cut rates at every meeting though June, f...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BNP Boosts SRT a Second Time to Back €17 Billion of Loans</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449148316&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BNP Paribas SA increased the size of a corporate loan portfolio linked to a significant risk transfer for a second time, according to people familiar with the matter, providing the latest sign of growing investor demand for these transactions. 
The lender bolstered the pool of debt to...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Swiss Probe of Credit Suisse Nears With UBS Capital at Stake</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449136772&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Switzerland is nearing publication of a landmark political inquiry into the causes of Credit Suisse’s 2023 downfall, a report which is likely to apportion blame for the crisis and set the tone for the future regulation of UBS Group AG. 
The commission working on it — known in Switzerl...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Why Talk of a Half-Point ECB Rate Cut Just Won’t Go Away</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449132220&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Investors and economists can’t quite shake the idea that the European Central Bank will deliver a bigger cut in interest rates over the coming months.
Despite most officials favoring “gradual” — read quarter-point — moves, traders refuse to rule out a reduction of twice that size at o...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS CEO Warns Markets Risk Being Rattled by Tariffs, Politics</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449132217&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The incoming US administration’s potential move to raise tariffs on trading partners could combine with conflicts around the globe to increase risk in financial markets next year, according to the chief executive of UBS Group AG. 
“The acceleration of geopolitical events coupled with ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bafin warnt eindringlich: Wer hier Aktien kauft, der könnte alles verlieren</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449171690&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Vor diesem Angebot für Anleger hat die Bafin in einer neuerlichen Mitteilung eindringlich gewarnt. Denn wer hier Aktien kauft, der könnte im schlimmsten Fall wirklich alles verlieren. Das müssen Sie jetzt daher unbedingt wissen.
Immer wieder kommt es vor, dass Anleger durch betrügerische Angebote im...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vermögensverwalter AGI und Amundi stoppen Gespräche</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449173034&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 10.12.2024
Bloomberg/Reuters Frankfurt – Die Gespräche zwischen Allianz und Amundi über eine mögliche Fusion von Allianz Global Investors (AGI) mit dem französischen Vermögensverwalter sind vorerst gescheitert. Laut Insidern scheiterte die Einigung an der Struktur und Kontrolle des m...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS-CEO Ermotti: «An den Märkten werden wir grosse Volatilität erleben»</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449138613&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>«Die Beschleunigung geopolitischer Ereignisse gepaart mit einer Eskalation an den makroökonomischen Fronten - Zölle, Protektionismus - ist definitiv etwas, das man im Auge behalten muss», sagte UBS-CEO Sergio Ermotti im Gespräch mit Bloomberg TV. «Es ist immer noch sehr unsicher, an den Märkten werd...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aktie von Swiss Re im Hoch: So setzten Anleger auf weitere Gewinne</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2449166551&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Georg Pröbstl
Das hatte niemand mehr erwartet. Viele Jahre lang, zwischen 2013 und 2019 und von 2020 bis Anfang 2024 war die Aktie von Swiss Re ziemlich stabil in einer Seitwärtsspanne zwischen etwa 75 und 100 Franken müde vor sich hingelaufen. 2020 kam es zwar zum Jahresanfang zu einem Ausbruch auf...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>