<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Der Einsatz von KI-Systemen im Finanzsektor</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=667413612454039260</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Alle reden von KI, kaum jemand setzt sich aber mit den bereits in Kraft befindlichen Regeln für die KI-Nutzung auseinander. Vor Kurzem hat mir ein IT-Spezialist erzählt, sie hätten sich einen Tag in den Internetknoten eines Unternehmens aus dem Finanzsektor „gehängt“ und festgestellt, die Mitarbeite...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>InhaltSonderthemen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8448481780456800366</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Personen
News 6
Studien
Aktuelle Marktuntersuchungen 16
AssCompact Maklerservice 2025: Wie Makler die Servicequalität der Versicherer bewerten 18
Assekuranz
News 20
Alternative Investments: Chancen jenseits des Gewohnten 28
Eric Sauerborn und Daniel Große, Württembergische
Finanzielle Unabhängigkeit...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Auf der Krypto-Welle reiten</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=1790667511930567247</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Etablierte Kryptowährungen wie Bitcoin sind längst kein spekulatives Asset für ausschließlich risikofreudige Zocker mehr. Spätestens seit der umfassenden Regulierung durch die „Markets in Crypto Assets“-Verordnung (MiCA) sind Bitcoin und Co. in der Europäischen Union eine vollwertige Asset-Klasse, d...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Das unterscheidet Cathie Woods Rüstungs-ETF von anderen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18436488741243821999</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Der Rüstungsboom an der Börse hat auch die Fondsbranche erreicht. Allein in diesem Jahr sind mehr als ein Dutzend neuer Verteidigungsfonds für europäische Anlegerinnen und Anleger auf den Markt gekommen. Im September zählten die beiden größten Börsenfonds (ETFs) für den Sektor zu den meistgehandelte...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Zwischen Aufbruch und Umsetzung</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4372116107740857620</link>
<author>kurier.at</author>
<description>Österreich setzt seit Jahren konsequent auf den Ausbau erneuerbarer Energien – mit ambitionierten Zielen und wachsendem Handlungsdruck, denn bis 2040 will Österreich klimaneutral sein. Bereits heute stammen rund 80 Prozent des heimischen Stroms aus erneuerbaren Quellen, vor allem aus Wasserkraft. Do...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>„Infrastruktur ist Zukunft“ | 31.10.2025, 11:49 Goal Goal Yellow Card Red Card Verwarnung Times © Sabine Klimpt Slide 1 von 1</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12252084129094879740</link>
<author>kurier.at</author>
<description>Von Stephan Scopetta
Energiewende, Digitalisierung und Urbanisierung erfordern enorme Investitionen. Staaten können das nicht allein stemmen, privates Kapital wird immer wichtiger. Infrastrukturprojekte sichern Wachstum sowie Wettbewerbsfähigkeit und bieten stabile Erträge für Anleger. Die Geschäfts...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Meta, xAI Starting Trend for Billions in Off-Balance Sheet Debt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10208096562661026956</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Just this month, Meta Platforms Inc. has secured about $60 billion in capital to build data centers, part of its spending to get ahead in the artificial intelligence race. Half of that won’t show up on the social media giant’s balance sheet as debt. 
Meta is among firms popularizing a...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UK Bank Tax Jitters Grip City of London as Reeves’s Budget Nears</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12193194108037088634</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Britain’s Labour government has consistently assured City of London bankers that their corporate taxes won’t go up. Privately, executives are more worried than ever that ministers will hit them with a tax hike.
Major high street lenders and Wall Street names are bracing themselves for...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>French Inflation Slows Further Below ECB Target on Energy, Food</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16837680188795052431</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- French inflation slowed further below the European Central Bank’s target in October as energy costs dropped and food-price increases eased.
The reading for the euro area’s second-largest economy came in at an annual 0.9% following September’s 1.1%, statistics agency Insee said Friday....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kocher Says Data Have Turned ‘Slightly Better’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=1085846036712960010</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Martin Kocher said recent economic reports have improved a little and inflation is set to remain close to 2% for the next two years.
Speaking a day after third-quarter output numbers for the euro zone came in higher than anticipated, the ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s US Capital Markets Head Departs After Four Years</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3493248440404738682</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc.’s head of US capital markets Jackie Krese has left the company after four years, according to people familiar with the matter.
Her role as head of US BlackRock Capital Markets was a newly created position, in which Krese led a push to expand ESG, fund-raising, liquid sy...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Mustn’t Overreact to 2028 Inflation Forecasts, Kazaks Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13761525109577649413</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank must be careful in interpreting the inflation projections it will receive in December and avoid erratic policy decisions, according to Governing Council member Martins Kazaks.
While a first glimpse of estimated price trends in 2028 will help officials assess ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro-Zone Inflation Dips Closer to 2% as ECB Holds Rates</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6085879624236668323</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Euro-area inflation eased slightly but stayed above 2%, backing the European Central Bank’s decision to keep borrowing costs where they are.
Consumer prices rose 2.1% from a year ago in October, down from 2.2% in September. That matched the median estimate in a Bloomberg survey. A mea...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Position on Rates Is Good But Not Fixed, Villeroy Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11275967177179848980</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank’s monetary policy is well positioned but could yet shift as officials grapple with risks including those emanating from financial markets, Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau said.
The remarks follow the ECB’s decision to leave its deposit ra...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Italy’s Deputy Prime Minister Urges ECB to Cut Rates, Restart QE</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8376741670882594648</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Italian Deputy Prime Minister Antonio Tajani called on the European Central Bank to lower borrowing costs and resume quantitative easing to help prevent gains in the euro from hurting his country’s exporters.
“An ever-weaker dollar and an ever-stronger euro hurt our exporters on top o...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Altamir : Fidelity Management &[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10637461767249729639</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Altamir : Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company llc a franchi individuellement en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 4,99% du capital et des droits de vote (29/09/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Orange : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4560850021163698294</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Orange : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,59% du capital et 4,68% des droits de vote (23/10/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Alten : Fidelity Management &[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17226104504601166602</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Alten : Fidelity Management &amp;amp; Research Company llc, contrÎlée par la société FMR LLC, a franchi individuellement en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,63% du capital et 4,87% des droits de vote (14/10/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nexans : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15732772243043227467</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Nexans : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 4,95% du capital et des droits de vote (09/10/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ubisoft Entertainment : BlackRock, agissant[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7407803924891369000</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Ubisoft Entertainment : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 4,93% du capital et 4,46% des droits de vote (20/10/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mercialys : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12018103004732391432</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Mercialys : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds sous gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de et détient 4,95% du capital et des droits de vote (20/10/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Worldline : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2123296340323938757</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Worldline : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,54% du capital et 4,79% des droits de vote (16/10/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>