<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Simkus Says Two More Cuts Possible as Trade Hurts Economy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3876392750236376983</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
The European Central Bank may have to lower interest rates further as US tariffs weigh on economic growth and inflation continues to slow, according to Governing Council member Gediminas Simkus. 
After seven reductions sin...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Launches New Task Force to Simplify Banking Regulation</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3619251376142330567</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank has convened a task force led by some of its most powerful governors aimed at simplifying banking regulation, amid growing fears the region is falling behind. 
The central bank governors of Germany, France and Italy are among the key figures in the newly-conv...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Halbleiter-Krise? Diese Aktien leiden besonders unter den US-Zöllen - und diese eher nicht</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3208848119445610139</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Chip-Hersteller unter Druck: Die US-Zölle könnten einige Aktien aus der Branche hart treffen. Ein paar andere Papiere haben aber noch ganz gute Karten. Wir geben einen Überblick.
Es könnte zu einer erheblichen Bürde werden: Wie die Nachrichtenagentur Reuters nach Gesprächen mit Juristen und Experten...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wie werden Gold-Wertpapiere besteuert?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12640655605752744632</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Unser Leser hält das Edelmetall Gold indirekt, über besicherte Wertpapiere. Wie werden diese besteuert? Kann er ein gezahltes Verwahrentgelt absetzen?

Erstveröffentlichung: 2025-04-26 12:52:00 letzte Aktualisierung: 2025-04-26 12:52:04
WiWo Coachist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnente...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>