<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>UBS CEO Says Swiss Capital Plan Poses Risk of Overreaction</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456672145&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG Chief Executive Officer Sergio Ermotti said the bank is pushing back against the Swiss government’s proposals to make it hold substantially more capital, arguing that the design of new rules is over the top and will hurt competitiveness. 
The requirement to maintain 100% ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS CEO Signals Job Cuts Will Continue in Quest to Lower Costs</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456672128&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG Chief Executive Officer Sergio Ermotti said he will keep cutting headcount in the wake of the historic acquisition of Credit Suisse. 
The Swiss lender seeks to shed another $5.5 billion in costs in addition to the $7.5 billion already achieved since the deal, Ermotti said...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS’s Ermotti Analyzing Wall Street Retreat From Climate Group</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456664624&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG Chief Executive Officer Sergio Ermotti said he’s looking at whether to follow Wall Street peers in abandoning a key climate-finance alliance, as lenders seek to protect themselves from intensifying political pressure.
“I think that we have to carefully analyze the situati...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB to Near Inflation Target by Middle of Year, Nagel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456664613&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should be close to its 2% inflation goal by mid-2025, allowing it to lower interest rates to levels that no longer weigh on the economy, according to Governing Council member Joachim Nagel.
“We are on a good path to our target and it looks like that by the mi...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock, Weinstein Reach Truce in Spat on Closed-End Funds</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456664597&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. stuck agreements with Boaz Weinstein’s Saba Capital Management that will end the activist-hedge fund’s battle with BlackRock over dozens of closed-end funds whose share prices had tumbled deeply below the value of their underlying assets.
As part of the deal, BlackRock ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Villeroy Says It’s Plausible to Cut at Each Meeting</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456644816&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- It’s possible that the European Central Bank will lower interest rates at each of its upcoming meetings, according to Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau.
Officials’ task of bringing inflation back to 2% is on track, despite President Donald Trump’s threats of trade t...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Joins Banks Halting Margin Loans on New World Securities</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456639695&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG halted accepting some bonds and shares of New World Development Co. as collateral for margin loans, joining other global lenders in suspending such financing for rich clients, according to people familiar with the matter.
The wealth arm of the Swiss bank cut back the lend...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazimir Sees Three to Four More Cuts Starting Next Week</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456632823&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A reduction in interest rates next week by the European Central Bank is all but certain and two to three more will probably follow, according to Governing Council member Peter Kazimir.
Recent data suggest quarter-point, back-to-back rate cuts should continue, Kazimir said late Monday ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>J.P. Morgan warnt: Finger weg von diesen beliebten Aktien - Drohen Kursverluste?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456624209&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Von diesen Aktien sollten Anleger laut der Investmentbank J.P. Morgan jetzt die Finger lassen, so zumindest die Warnungen der Analysten. Drohen hier Kursverluste für Investoren?
In einer kürzlich veröffentlichten Studie hat die US-Investmentbank J.P. Morgan die besten taktischen Short-Ideen für das ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Immac bringt weiteren Dachfonds-AIF für Privatanleger</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456658526&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Cash.Online</author>
<description>Ab einer Investition von 10.000 Euro können sich Privatanleger und institutionelle Investoren an dem risikogemischten, geschlossenen alternativen Investmentfonds (AIF) zu beteiligen, teilt Immac mit. Der Fonds investiert in mindestens drei unterschiedliche Zielinvestments der Immac Group.
Die Fondsg...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>