<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Use of BlackRock Tokens as Collateral Moves Closer to Mainstream</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436125810&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Efforts to allow use of tokenized shares of money-market funds from Wall Street behemoths like BlackRock and Franklin Templeton as collateral in trading took a big step forward as a group of financial firms voted to approve guidelines for their use.
A subcommittee of the Commodity Fut...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Can’t Ignore Headwinds to Economic Growth, Schnabel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436120313&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank must address the euro area’s disappointing economic performance, according to Executive Board member Isabel Schnabel. 
“We cannot ignore the headwinds to growth,” she said in Freiburg, Germany. “With signs of softening labor demand and further progress in dis...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fidelity Raises First Fund Dedicated to Venture Capital</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436108402&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Fidelity Investments has raised $250 million for its first fund dedicated to venture capital investments, pushing the firm further into private assets. 
Fidelity Venture Capital Fund I closed with backing from family offices, investment advisers and high-net worth individuals, the Bos...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Leans Toward October Cut But Warns Markets</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436092106&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is likely to lower borrowing costs at this month’s meeting and beyond, but some investors’ and economists’ easing expectations appear exaggerated, according to Governing Council member Martins Kazaks.
“We will discuss and decide when we meet next time and wil...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Chases Private Credit Deals in Record India Market</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436092099&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for the India Edition newsletter by Menaka Doshi – an insider's guide to the emerging economic powerhouse, and the billionaires and businesses behind its rise, delivered weekly.
BlackRock Inc., the world’s largest asset manager, is hunting for Indian direct lending opportuniti...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Momentum for an October Rate Cut Is Looking Unstoppable</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436092093&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- An interest-rate cut that European Central Bank officials deemed unlikely just three weeks ago now seems a near certainty when they next set borrowing costs on Oct. 17.
Markedly souring business surveys, the first below-2% inflation reading in more than three years and the reassurance...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Guindos Says Euro Zone’s Economic Recovery Will Strengthen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436086708&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The economic revival in the euro area is likely to gain momentum, though dangers remain, according to European Central Bank Vice President Luis de Guindos.
In a speech in Riga that didn’t touch on monetary policy, Guindos warned that risks in the 20-nation bloc are still “tilted to th...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BaFin mahnt bei Prämiensparen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436119355&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 3.10.2024
Die Bundesanstalt für Finanzdienstleistungsaufsicht (BaFin) hat Verbrauchern empfohlen, ihre Prämiensparverträge auf mögliche Nachzahlungsansprüche zu überprüfen. Dies folgt aus zwei Urteilen des Bundesgerichtshofs (BGH) vom 9. Juli 2024, in denen erstmals ein Referenzzinss...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bafin rät Sparern, Ansprüche bei Prämiensparverträgen zu prüfen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436117613&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>capital.de</author>
<description>Die Finanzaufsicht Bafin rät Besitzern von Prämiensparverträgen, dringend mögliche Nachzahlungsansprüche zu prüfen. „Insbesondere Inhaberinnen und Inhaber älterer Prämiensparverträge könnten Anspruch auf Nachzahlungen haben“, erklärte die Behörde mit Verweis auf einen Entscheid des Bundesgerichtshof...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Procimmo Real Estate SICAV legt 1. Jahresabschluss vor und plant Kapitalerhöhung</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436084892&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Der an der Schweizer Börse SIX kotierte Fonds war erst im Oktober 2023 aus der Fusion der beiden Fonds «Swiss Commercial Fund» und «Swiss Commercial Fund II» entstanden. Das «ausgezeichnete» Ergebnis bestätige die Finanzkraft des grössten industriellen Immobilienfonds der Schweiz, teilte dieser am M...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>