<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>HPE Rises to Record on Strong Sales With Boost From AI Servers</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448674670&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Hewlett Packard Enterprise Co. reached a record high after reporting better-than-expected quarterly revenue and a jump in sales of servers to power artificial intelligence work.
Demand for high-powered computing to run AI workloads has led to a boom for hardware makers, including HPE,...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Is Said to Quiz Some Banks About SRT Buyers’ Leverage</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448651081&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is seeking clarity on how investors use borrowed money to buy significant risk transfers, as it tries to ensure the increasingly popular structure helps mitigate exposures rather than shift them across the banking sector.
The supervisor sent a questionnaire t...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Big Bet on GIP Puts Fink’s Firm in Local Spotlight</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448651075&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- In the port city of Duluth, Minnesota, local activists and Washington-based groups are coalescing to scrutinize — and possibly stall — a $6.2 billion acquisition of a power utility led by Global Infrastructure Partners.
More than 8,000 miles away, GIP’s role in a multibillion-dollar d...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>PTT Is Said to Pick UBS, Bualuang to Work on Downstream Review</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448643900&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Thai oil and gas firm PTT Pcl has picked financial advisers for a review of its downstream businesses as it seeks to run them more efficiently and boost their valuations, according to people with knowledge of the matter.
PTT is working with Bangkok Bank Pcl’s Bualuang Securities Pcl a...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Seeks to Speed Up Approvals for SRT Deal as Demand Grows</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448637502&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is seeking to accelerate its approval process for significant risk transfers, according to people familiar with the matter, helping lenders to take advantage of booming demand for the deals.
Under new proposals, banks will be allowed to submit information for...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB to Cut Faster in Bid to Revive Flagging Economy, Poll Shows</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448632692&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank will cut interest rates more rapidly than previously envisaged to perk up an economy facing weaker growth and inflation, a Bloomberg survey showed.
Respondents predict a quarter-point reduction next week and at every policy meeting through June — taking the d...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Private Markets auf dem Weg zur Börse</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448676256&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 7 . 12 . 2024
tl Hamburg
Der auf Private Markets spezialisierte virtuelle Marktplatz Finexity will verstärkt mit dem Sparkassensektor zusammenarbeiten. Das 2018 gegründete Unternehmen, das bereits mit der Sparkasse Bremen kooperiert, will Anlegern auch mit geringem Kapitaleinsatz Pri...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Baloise-Immobilienfonds Swiss Property steigert Erträge und erhöht Ausschüttung</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448632177&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Nun soll die Ausschüttung um 0,10 Franken auf neu 3,10 Franken je Anteil angehoben werden. Grund für die Ertragssteigerung sind laut einer Mitteilung sechs Immobilienzukäufe und Mietertragssteigerungen im Bestand. Weiter habe die Mietausfallrate zum dritten Mal in Folge reduziert werden können, näml...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aktie der UBS erhält höheres Kursziel</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448641788&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Die Aktie der UBS ist am Freitag in einem leicht negativen Gesamtmarkt kaum verändert bei 28,96 Franken. Der Titel hat in diesem Jahr 11 Prozent zugelegt.
JPMorgan erhöhte am Freitag in einer Branchenstudie das Kursziel für die UBS-Aktie auf 34 von zuvor 31 Franken. Die Einstufung "Overweight" wurde...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Meta-Aktie im Aufwind: Zeit zum Einsteigen für Investoren?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2448646673&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Georg Pröbstl
In den nächsten Wochen und zumindest im ersten Quartal 2025 könnte die Aktie von Meta weiter steigen. In den letzten zwei Jahren, seit Anfang 2023, ist die Aktie des Betreibers der Social-Media-Plattform Facebook und Experten für künstliche Intelligenz (KI) ohnehin einer der Top-Perfor...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>