<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Spottbillige Lufthansa-Aktie: So können Anleger spekulieren</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15412076160738939025</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Georg Pröbstl
Seit Besprechung der Lufthansa-Aktie Mitte Juni ging der Kurs schon um bis zu rund 15 Prozent nach oben. Die damals ebenfalls zum Kauf empfohlenen Calls auf das MDAX-Mitglied lagen bis vor wenigen Tagen sogar bis 200 Prozent im Gewinn. Das ist eine Verdreifachung in nur drei Monaten.
I...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>US-Shutdown bremst Statistik, nicht die Märkte</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13992247879164060782</link>
<author>FOCUS online</author>
<description>Anders als etwa in Deutschland muss die US-Regierung ihre nicht systemrelevanten Ausgaben stoppen, wenn sich das Parlament über den Haushalt nicht einigen kann. Dieser Zustand führt zu Beeinträchtigungen bei öffentlichen Leistungen, ist aber für die Wirtschaft insgesamt nicht bedrohlich, zumal die S...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vanguard Fund Overtakes BlackRock as Muni Market’s Biggest ETF</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=389512535517643127</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Competition is heating up in the rapidly growing arena of municipal-bond exchange-traded funds. 
The Vanguard Tax-Exempt Bond ETF (ticker VTEB) now has $39.9 billion in assets after drawing in $4.3 billion so far this year, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. That has nudged it j...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lagarde Says ECB Has Done a Lot on Rates, Is in ‘Good Place’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5785499733816038717</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde suggested that she’s comfortable with the current policy settings as inflation in the euro area remains broadly stable.
“We are in a good place and we have to make sure that we stay in that good place,” she told Finland’s MTV OY in an ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s $40 Billion Bet on a Lesser-Known Data Center Firm</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17940159346328694099</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- At the start of the year, a lesser-known infrastructure company called Aligned Data Centers managed to pull off a $12 billion fundraise — more than some of the world’s leading artificial intelligence startups have been able to secure in a single round. The goal: dramatically expanding...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Should Cut Rates to Boost Economy, Italy’s Finance Chief Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2350470525257884517</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should reduce borrowing costs to help the euro-area economy, Italian Finance Minister Giancarlo Giorgetti said.
“The ECB’s monetary policy is no longer restrictive like in past years, but overall stagnation of the European economy leads us to believe that — w...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Rates in Good Place to Deliver Stable Inflation, Wunsch Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11298650428687913439</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank’s policy settings are appropriate to ensure consumer prices are rising in line with the 2% target in the medium term, according to Governing Council member Pierre Wunsch.
Officials found the “perfect calibration” for interest rates “after we started really fi...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vanguard Rivals Finally Get Hands On Its Tax-Busting Fund Design</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9433213697236888155</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- For more than two decades, US money managers have looked on enviously as Vanguard Group reaped the benefits of a unique structure that grafted the advantages of an ETF onto its biggest mutual funds. The design, protected by patent, saved its investors billions of dollars and helped th...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lagarde Says Knot Would Make a Good ECB President, ANP Reports</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7867089085520977314</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde said Klaas Knot would be a suitable successor, Dutch newswire ANP reported, citing a podcast episode of “College Leaders in Finance,” which will be released on Sunday.
“I’ve known him for at least six years. He has the intellect, the s...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Lagarde Calls for Non-Banks to Face Tougher Scrutiny</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7521181563734667443</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde warned against lowering standards in banking regulation, arguing that scrutiny of non-banks must be strengthened instead.
After years of enhancing supervision since the Great Financial Crisis, it’s time to take a closer look at the rul...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Schnabel Says Financial Markets May Be Getting Complacent</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8772313314010801840</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Executive member Isabel Schnabel said that investor and other financial market participants are possibly underestimating risks.
“Unfortunately we cannot fully rule that out,” she said Friday in Amsterdam when discussing the question whether markets have become co...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>