<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>MACHER OHNE GRENZEN</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451353608&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bilanz (Schweiz)</author>
<description>von ERICH BÜRGLER
Christian Kälin wollte eigentlich zu einer Grossbank. Als junger Mann bewarb er sich um eine Lehrstelle sowohl bei der UBS als auch bei der CS, die damals noch SKA hiess – ohne Erfolg. «Ich bin bei beiden Aufnahmeprüfungen durchgefallen», erzählt der 53-Jährige. Heute denkt Kälin d...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Clever investieren dank bewährter Strategien für die Geldanlage</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451353335&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bilanz (Schweiz)</author>
<description>Nur wenn man weiss, wo man steht, kann man bestimmen, wohin die Reise geht. Diese (zugegebenermassen etwas hobby-philosophisch anmutende) Aussage hat insbesondere im Bereich Vermögensverwaltung Gültigkeit. Denn wie jeder Finanzprofi weiss: Ein durchdachter Vermögensplan beginnt mit einer genauen Ana...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>«Wir eilen keinen Hypes nach»</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451353328&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bilanz (Schweiz)</author>
<description>Innovation und Dynamik sind Schlagwörter, mit denen sich viele Firmen gerne schmücken. Und so wichtig diese Qualitäten für den Werkplatz Schweiz auch sind – gerade im Finanzsektor sind Beständigkeit sowie eine langfristige Strategie mindestens ebenso relevant. Den Beweis dafür erbringt seit Jahren d...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Opened Credit Line to Oil Firm 3 Months Before UK Sanctions</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451398820&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG opened a credit line to commodity trader 2Rivers, three months before the company was sanctioned by the UK government, which declared it a “lynchpin” of Russian oil flows.
2Rivers emerged earlier this year, in a rebranding of Coral Energy Group following a management buyo...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Mulls Job Cuts In France on Weak Economy, CS Integration</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451398795&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG is looking at enacting job cuts in France in response to the country’s deteriorating economic outlook and the ongoing combination with Credit Suisse.
“Due to a less favorable market environment and after the integration of Credit Suisse earlier this year, UBS is consideri...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS’ Zhao Plans to Buy US Bonds Before Trump Policies Hit Growth</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451398794&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Asset Management’s Kevin Zhao plans to keep working during the holidays this year, hoping that if US Treasuries selloff amid thin trading volumes he’ll be there to buy.
Zhao, a portfolio manager at the Swiss investment house, is betting that President-elect Donald Trump’s policies...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Revolut’s European Unit Faces Highest ECB Capital Requirement</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451379858&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Revolut Ltd.’s European unit faces the highest individual capital requirement set by the European Central Bank for significant lenders in the region, as the fintech pursues rapid growth to challenge traditional banks.
The ECB assigned Revolut Holdings Europe UAB a Pillar 2 Requirement...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Nagel Sees Rates at Neutral in First Half of 2025: Focus</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451366091&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Joachim Nagel expects euro-area interest rates to reach a level that no longer restricts economic activity in the first half of next year as inflation is “well under control.”
“We can certainly lower interest rates a little further,” the ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Immobilienfonds La Foncière mit höherem Ergebnis 23/24 und Dividendensteigerung</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451360255&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Die Mietzinseinnahmen erhöhten sich dank der Fertigstellung zweier Entwicklungsprojekte in Genf um 7,9 Prozent auf 92,7 Millionen Franken, wie die Fondsleitung der Investissements Fonciers SA am Freitag mitteilte. Die Leerstandsquote lag mit sehr tiefen 0,66 Prozent nochmals leicht unter dem Niveau ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS unterstützt "die meisten" BR-Vorschläge zur Stärkung des Finanzplatzes</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2451370506&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Die UBS unterstütze «die meisten» Vorschläge des Bundesrats zur Stärkung der Resilienz des Finanzplatzes, erklärte die Grossbank weiter. Allfällige Anpassungen der regulatorischen Anforderungen müssten aber «zielgerichtet, proportional und international abgestimmt» sein.
Dabei müssten die Finanzstab...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>