<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Schnabel Says Euro Zone Stagnating, Disinflation on Track</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434944706&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Executive Board member Isabel Schnabel appears to have become more concerned about the euro-zone economy. 
In a presentation for an event Thursday in Stuttgart, she said the “euro-area economy is stagnating,” that “surveys signal slowing economy” and that there a...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mexico’s Peso to Gain as Political Uncertainty Ebbs, UBS Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434929694&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Mexico’s peso is set to strengthen through the first half of next year as investors grow more comfortable with the new administration and volatility around the US election fades, according to UBS Group AG.
The currency should gain around 5% from current levels to 18.50 per dollar by t...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock to Invest $1 Billion a Year in Banco Santander Loans</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434911441&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. will invest as much as $1 billion a year in energy and project finance assets from Banco Santander SA, signaling another step in the money manager’s growing expansion this year into infrastructure.
The move deepens a partnership with Santander that has included BlackRoc...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Commerzbank Board Hires UBS for Potential UniCredit Deal Advice</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434911439&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Commerzbank AG’s supervisory board has mandated UBS Group AG to help it navigate a potential takeover bid from UniCredit SpA, according to a person familiar with the matter, who asked not to be named discussing private information. 
UniCredit earlier this month disclosed a 21% stake i...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Schroders Names Burnett as Finance Chief, CIO Kyrklund to Board</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434897836&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Schroders Plc named operations head Meagen Burnett as its chief financial officer and appointed Chief Investment Officer Johanna Kyrklund to the board.
Burnett joined Schroders last year and she will be succeeding Richard Oldfield, who’s set to become chief executive officer on Nov. 8...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Jewell Says Stocks Can Cope With Earnings Downgrades</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434888334&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- While global corporate earnings estimates for the rest of the year appear optimistic, stock markets are likely to be able to absorb moderate downgrades for now, according to BlackRock Inc.’s Helen Jewell.
Profit projections for 2024 have been “back-ended” into the second half, and “I ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Infrastrukturfonds von SFP erreicht 110 Millionen Euro</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434895226&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>SFP hatte ihr Engagement im Infrastrukturbereich im April 2022 angekündigt. Die neu gegründete SFP Infrastructure Partners solle aktiv Opportunitäten im traditionellen Infrastrukturbereich verfolgen, hiess es seinerzeit. Dabei wurde für den in Luxemburg domizilierten Fonds eine Zielgrösse von 250 Mi...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Immofonds erlöst mit Kapitalerhöhung knapp 150 Millionen Franken</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434895225&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Mit den frischen Mitteln sollen mehrheitlich die zweite Bauetappe des Grossprojekts Wankdorfcity 3 in Bern und der nachhaltige Ausbau des Portfolios finanziert werden, wie die Immofonds Asset Management AG am Donnerstag mitteilte. Die Kapitalerhöhung erfolgte unter Wahrung der Bezugsrechte der bishe...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ermotti vs. Orcel: UBS soll Commerzbank bei Unicredit-Angriff helfen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434895221&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>cash Insider
Das ist an den Märkten passiert
Commerzbank holt sich noch mehr Beratung gegen Angriff aus Mailand. Neu soll auch UBS subito Vorschläge ausarbeiten, wie sich Commerzbank gegen den Übernahmeversuch von Unicredit zur Wehr setzen kann. Auch Goldman Sachs soll dabei helfen. Das berichtet "B...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Swiss Prime Anlagestiftung investiert in Wohnprojekt in Genf</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2434918085&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Auf dem Baufeld D im Genfer Stadtteil Cherpines sollen auf einer Fläche von knapp 15'000 Quadratmetern 175 Mietwohnungen entstehen, teilte die Anlagestiftung am Donnerstag mit. Das Projekt sei Teil einer grösseren Entwicklung, die rund 3000 Wohneinheiten und 2000 Arbeitsplätze umfasse. In unmittelba...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>