<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>J.P. Morgan warnt: Von diesen beliebten Aktien sollten Anleger jetzt die Finger lassen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12533965521190354348</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Laut einer aktuellen Studie von J.P. Morgan sollten sich Anleger ausgerechnet jetzt vor diesen beliebten Aktien hüten. Darum zeigt sich hier ein Verkaufssignal, das nicht nur für die einzelnen Werte, sondern für den ganzen Markt gelten könnte.
In einer neuen Analyse schlägt das Strategieteam von J.P...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rising Fiscal Deficits Drive Billions Into Credit</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15251572336584304310</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Investors are showing signs of pulling money out of government bonds and plowing it into US and European company debt.   
If the moves persist, money managers could be shifting what for decades has been market orthodoxy: that nothing is safer than buying US government debt. But as US ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Charting the Global Economy: ECB Holds for First Time in a Year</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3939548373777167736</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank kept interest rates unchanged for the first time in more than a year as it looks for clarity on the European Union’s trade ties with the US.
Policymakers pushing for another cut in interest rates face an uphill battle, with inflation at 2% and the economy wit...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Cipollone Is Seeing ‘Conflicting Signals’ in Economy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=307610888951760315</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Executive Board member Piero Cipollone said the economy is sending “conflicting signals” as officials wait for more clarity before taking a fresh view on whether interest rates need to be lowered any further. 
In an interview with Slovenian newspaper Delo, Cipoll...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>