<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Klaus Hessberger wechselt von J.P. Morgan zu Lazard</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10071657952865145882</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Die Investmentbank Lazard hat Klaus Hessberger, einen der ranghöchsten Private-Equity-Dealmaker von J.P. Morgan, bei dem großen US-Konkurrenten abgeworben. Klaus H. Hessberger wird Managing Director, Global Co-Head und Head of Europe der Financial Sponsors Group bei Lazard. Die Börsen-Zeitung hatte ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>„Wir befinden uns an einem Wendepunkt“</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3345691749997867271</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Agentenbasierte künstliche Intelligenz ermöglicht der Finanzbranche enormen Produktivitätsschub

Digitale Arbeitskräfte werden für einen enormen Produktivitätsschub in der Finanzbranche sorgen. Agentenbasierte künstliche Intelligenz liefert die Chance, die Belegschaft unbegrenzt auszuweiten. „Wir be...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Virtuelle Mitarbeiter</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4655825138973866749</link>
<author>Gewinn</author>
<description>Was KI-Agenten von Chatbots unterscheidet und wie sie dabei helfen können, dass Fachkräfte effizienter und wertschöpfender arbeiten.
Was ist der wesentliche Unterschied zwischen den USA und Europa? Die Effizienz.
„In den USA gilt eine einfache Regel: Alles, was an repetitiven Aufgaben automatisiert ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Selbst ernannte Finanzcoaches</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=516882545783548241</link>
<author>Gewinn</author>
<description>Viele, gerade Junge, wollen ihre Finanzen selbst in die Hand nehmen und belegen am Weg dorthin oft auf Social Media beworbene, gar nicht so billige Onlinekurse, Trainings oder als exklusiv angepriesene Schulungen bei diversen Finanzcoaches. Sie schließen als „profitables Investment“ angepriesene Abo...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Swiss Prime Anlagestiftung schliesst Kapitalerhöhung ab</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8054435349677360731</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Die Swiss Prime Anlagestiftung (SPA) hat eine Kapitalerhöhung des Fonds «SPA Immobilien Schweiz» abgeschlossen.

Das ursprünglich geplante Volumen von 150 Millionen Franken sei deutlich überzeichnet worden, heisst es in einer Mitteilung vom Dienstag. Aufgrund der hohen Nachfrage habe der Stiftungsra...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Der Immobilienverkauf stockt. Was nun?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9979629353158430021</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Unsere Leserin und ihr Mann wollen ein geerbtes Haus bei Kassel verkaufen, aus den 1950er-Jahren. Das Interesse ist überschaubar. Welche Strategien eignen sich?

WiWo Coach ist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnenten. Top-Experten beantworten hier all Ihre Fragen rund um Geldanlage, Vorso...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wie sich Enterbte über den Nachlass informieren können</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9777994901603971935</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Einem Leser steht ein Pflichtteil am Erbe seines Vaters zu. Er will Einblick in den Nachlass. Anwalt Claus-Henrik Horn erklärt, wie das geht.

WiWo Coach ist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnenten. Top-Experten beantworten hier all Ihre Fragen rund um Geldanlage, Vorsorge, Karriere, Steu...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wie sicher ist meine Arbeit vor KI? Was aktuelle Daten zeigen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13911581873134110678</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Eine Datenanalyse des Handelsblatts zeigt: Erste Berufsgruppen merken bereits jetzt Effekte der KI-Revolution. Einige betroffene Jobs überraschen dabei selbst Expertinnen.

Die Zukunftsfragen könnten größer nicht sein. Stehen in Deutschland wegen Künstlicher Intelligenz (KI) drei Millionen Berufstät...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bei Physical AI kann Europa weltweit in Führung gehen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10659408658200063015</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Der nächste Technologiesprung liegt nicht in Sprachmodellen, sondern im Training von Maschinen. Dafür hat Europa die besten Karten, meinen Thomas Kropf, Philipp Harbach und Markus Hoffmann.

Bei der Künstlichen Intelligenz beherrschen zwar Sprach‑ und Bildmodelle die Schlagzeilen, doch der nächste T...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sind Finfluencer wirklich Vermittler?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11887680843169894608</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Neulich auf der Hauptversammlung des BVK: Nach einem Impulsvortrag des Rechtswissenschaftlers Prof. Schwintowski zum Thema Finfluencer antwortete BVK-Präsident Heinz auf die Frage der Moderatorin, was er fühle, wenn er sehe, dass jemand mit drei Emojis und einem ETF-Video 400.000 Follower begeistere...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Quo vadis, Honorarberatung?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14930456475625070726</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Steuerberater, Rechtsanwälte, Unternehmensberater aller Art haben eines gemeinsam: Die Vergütung ihrer Dienstleistung erfolgt auf Honorarbasis. Auch wer in der Finanzbranche Kundinnen und Kunden berät, bietet eine wichtige Dienstleistung an. Doch diese wird oft erst dann vergütet, wenn der Kunde ein...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vanguard Plans First Junk ETF as JPMorgan Heats Up Active Race</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15848729516329668425</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Vanguard Group is planning its debut into an increasingly competitive corner of the $11.6 trillion US exchange-traded fund arena.
The Vanguard High-Yield Active ETF would trade under the ticker VGHY and invest at least 80% of its portfolio in high-yield debt, according to a Tuesday fi...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Says Consumers’ Inflation Expectations Declined In May</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8417554769508051946</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Inflation expectations of euro-area consumers eased in May, the European Central Bank said.
Prices were seen increasing 2.8% over the next 12 months, down from 3.1% in April, according to a monthly survey released Tuesday. The gauge for three years fell to 2.4% from 2.5%, while for fi...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Muller Sees No Need for Rate Cuts to Stimulate Economy Now</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8730935081119943415</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Madis Muller said the economy doesn’t currently justify interest rates that stimulate growth, allowing officials to take a pause from easing to gauge how activity withstands various threats.
After eight cuts since June 2024 and inflation ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Guindos Says Euro Gain Past $1.20 Would Be Complicated</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6400643373559824834</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Vice President Luis de Guindos said an advance in the euro beyond $1.20 could prove tricky for policymakers but current levels aren’t cause for concern.
In rare remarks by an ECB official on the common currency’s exchange rate, Guindos told Bloomberg TV that the ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Simkus Warns of Fragile Inflation Path Due to Euro, Energy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3317594062257360111</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank has fulfilled its inflation goal but volatility in foreign-exchange and commodities markets means the outlook for prices is murky, according to Governing Council member Gediminas Simkus. 
The rapid strengthening of the euro against the dollar and moves in ene...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UniCredit to Offer BlackRock Bitcoin ETF-Linked Product for Some Clients</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6676465807643313687</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UniCredit SpA will offer its professional clients a structured product tied to BlackRock Inc.’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF that features full protection against losses, as European banks seek new ways to tap into appetite for digital assets. 
The bank plans to issue a five-year, dollar...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Gets Another ‘Moderate Hawk’ as Dutch Central-Bank Veteran Exits</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17212813556160962794</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Olaf Sleijpen, the European Central Bank’s newest interest-rate setter, is about to continue where his Dutch predecessor left off. 
The 54-year-old economist takes over as the head of the central bank of the Netherlands on Tuesday, succeeding the hawkish Klaas Knot, who was among the ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Capital Group’s Gitlin Says Better Valuations Seen Away From US</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6320595597709989688</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Capital Group CEO Mike Gitlin said investors are eyeing diversification away from the US given the compelling opportunities elsewhere, and the risks stemming from geopolitics and supply-chain disruptions.
“While US comprises 70% of the MSCI All World Index, our investors are seeing pl...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Wonders Whether Euro Rally Will Turn From Blessing to Curse</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4662869219673847194</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank officials are starting to fret that a rapid appreciation of the euro could derail efforts to anchor inflation at 2%.
The single currency is up about 14% against the dollar this year as confidence in the US dwindles — helping curb price gains that now precisely ma...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>HPS Struts Into BlackRock as Fink Bets Big on Private Credit</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5241673646827521142</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Scott Kapnick could afford to swagger as he feted his partners at The Modern, the elegant restaurant at the Museum of Modern Art in Manhattan.
So could his colleagues: Kapnick’s HPS Investment Partners, a major player in the fast-growing market for private credit, was about to join fo...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Escriva Says Symmetric 2% Goal Should Remain ECB’s Primary Guide</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9448902366716708161</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is right to focus on a symmetric 2% inflation target, according to Governing Council member Jose Luis Escriva.
That goals “has been key to keeping inflation expectations anchored over the years, even during recent episodes of high inflation, and should remain...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro-Zone Inflation Ticks Higher to Match ECB’s 2% Target</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2992619627169307034</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Euro-area inflation settled at the European Central Bank’s target in June, strengthening arguments to press pause on a year-long campaign of interest-rate cuts.
Consumer prices rose 2% from a year ago, up from May’s 1.9%, Eurostat said Tuesday. That matched the median estimate in a Bl...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Says Any Further Rate Adjustments Won’t Be Big</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12906233344858214480</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank will make minor changes to borrowing costs at best as long as the economy develops in line with the most recent projections, according to Governing Council member Martins Kazaks.
With inflation at the 2% target and the region still growing, there’s no need fo...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Keeps Hold of Worldline Bonds Amid Alleged Fraud Reports</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18283012853263155081</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank held on to two bonds of embattled payments company Worldline SA while prices slumped following news reports alleging that the company covered up fraud by some of its customers.
A €500 million ($591 million) note due 2027 and a €600 million issue maturing in 2...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Nagel Sees Inflation in ‘Calmer Waters’ But Caution Needed</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11811616821713570128</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank has brought inflation under control but mustn’t become complacent due to the highly volatile geopolitical backdrop, according to Governing Council member Joachim Nagel.
Speaking on the sidelines of the ECB’s annual retreat in Sintra, Portugal, Nagel said the ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>