<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Guindos Says ECB Sees ‘Substantial Risks’ to Inflation Outlook</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2441020898&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank has made significant progress in bringing down inflation but can’t declare victory just yet, according to Vice President Luis de Guindos.
“The incoming information shows that the disinflationary process is now well on track,” he said on Monday in Madrid. “The...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BNP Paribas Said to Lay Off Handful in Credit Sales, Trading</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2441010350&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BNP Paribas SA let go at least half a dozen employees in New York last week, including its head of US high-yield trading, David Malvern, according to people familiar with the matter. 
Two investment-grade credit traders were also let go, plus two sales employees, said the people, who ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trader Seeks €37.5 Million Payday on Faster ECB Rate Reductions</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2441006166&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- One trader is wagering huge sums that the European Central Bank will quicken the pace of interest-rate cuts to prop up the region’s economy. 
The trade, using options on futures tied to the three-month Euribor funding rate, will pay out €37.5 million ($40.6 million) on an initial €6 m...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nvidia Has Lots Riding on This Week Even as Earnings a Month Out</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440982979&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Nvidia Corp. isn’t expected to announce earnings for another month, but results this week from the chipmaker’s biggest customers are about to set the tone for its shares, which are trading near an all-time high on optimism around the AI boom.
Microsoft Corp., Alphabet Inc., Amazon.com...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Communications Are Getting Messy as Rate Cuts Advance</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440971681&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- So far, European Central Bank officials have mostly succeeded in steering the euro-zone economy toward 2% inflation with a single voice. But as they circle in on their target, views on what to do when are set to diverge.
Points of friction were already evident last week in Washington,...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carmakers’ Malaise, UBS’s Next Step: EMEA Earnings Week Ahead</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440971674&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A moment of truth beckons for carmakers Stellantis NV and Aston Martin Lagonda Global Holdings Plc, both of which slashed their forecasts in the run-up to this week’s earnings reports.
Listen to the Here’s Why podcast on Apple, Spotify or anywhere you listen.
While much of Fiat and Pe...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Streit um Bankenabgabe geht vor Gericht</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2441011295&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 29 . 10 . 2024
ahe Berlin
Der Streit um die Altmittel der Bankenabgabe wird jetzt vor Gericht weiter ausgefochten. Nach Informationen der Börsen-Zeitung haben mehrere Kreditinstitute jetzt eine Untätigkeitsklage gegen die Bundesanstalt für Finanzdienstleistungsaufsicht (BaFin) vor de...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS rät auf Rekordhoch zum Kauf von Aktien</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440976831&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>cash Insider
Das ist an den Märkten passiert
...überraschend die Kehrtwende: Neuerdings geht die grösste Schweizer Bank bei Aktien auf ATTRACTIVE (Neutral). Setzt vermehrt auf Aktien aus den USA und dort auf jene der Gewinner des KI-Booms. Zur Erinnerung: Die New Yorker Börse befindet sich auf Rekor...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>SNB: UBS steigt über ihre Fondstochter ein</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440988632&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>cash Insider
Der cash Insider berichtet auch im Insider Briefing jeweils vorbörslich von brandaktuellen Beobachtungen rund um das Schweizer Marktgeschehen und ist unter @cashInsider auf X/Twitter aktiv.
+++
Vergangenen Donnerstag berichtete ich in meiner Kolumne gleich bei mehreren Schweizer Unterne...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>