<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Villeroy Urges Agility on Rates to Not Fall Behind Curve</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439865414&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank must be agile with further interest-rate cuts to avoid the risk of acting too slowly, according to Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau. 
The Bank of France chief said persistently too-strong inflation is no longer the “sole and dominant risk”...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Rehn Says Weak Growth May Boost Disinflation Pressures</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439865401&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- An increasingly dire euro-area economy might exacerbate slowing consumer-price growth, according to European Central Bank Governing Council member Olli Rehn.
“Disinflation in the euro area is well on track,” the Finnish central-bank chief said Tuesday in Washington. “The growth outloo...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Saudi Arabia Taps BlackRock to Build Mortgage-Backed Securities Market</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439855990&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Arabia has hired the world’s biggest fund manager to help it develop a market for mortgage-backed securities as the kingdom looks to improve the affordability of its housing stock. 
The country hopes developing a secondary market for mortgages would allow banks to offer borrower...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Would Mull Bigger Cuts If Backed by Data, Centeno Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439850046&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank would be ready consider ramping up monetary easing should the data suggest such a move, according to Governing Council member Mario Centeno.
“If it’s gonna be 25 or at some point we have to do 50 that’s something data will tell us,” the Portuguese central-ban...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gensler Sees Potential Peril in $13 Trillion of Eurodollars</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439850023&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Wall Street’s top cop is sounding an alarm about the eurodollar market’s potential to foment instability in global economies, and he renewed warnings about risks embedded in private credit and artificial intelligence.
Much of the $13 trillion of US currency held offshore by non-US ban...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Holzmann Sees More ECB Rate Cuts in Not-Too-Distant Future</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439850015&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A faster-than-expected retreat in euro-zone inflation will allow the European Central Bank to cut interest rates again before too long, according to Governing Council member Robert Holzmann.
Last week’s decision to cut by a quarter point was the “right one,” Holzmann, one of the ECB’s...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nagel Dismisses Fed-Style ‘Dot Plot’ as ECB Rate-Signal Option</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439843764&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>Pursuits https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-22/nagel-dismisses-fed-style-dot-plot-as-ecb-rate-signal-option (Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank isn’t well suited for the Federal Reserve’s approach to signaling the future path of borrowing costs and should find other ways to improve...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fidelity Cuts 500 Jobs at China Support Center in Downsizing Bid</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439826650&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Fidelity International plans to cut about 500 jobs at a China-based global technology and support center as it expands efforts to trim costs, according to people with knowledge of the matter.
The asset manager will cut the positions at its technology and operational support center in ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BaFin warnt: Wer auf diese scheinbar seriöse E-Mail reagiert, der kann massiv Geld verlieren</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439827390&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Aktuell warnt die Bundesanstalt für Finanzdienstleistungsaufsicht (kurz BaFin) vor diesen scheinbar seriösen E-Mails. Denn wer darauf reagiert, der kann schnell massiv Geld an potenzielle Betrüger verlieren. Hier müssen Sparer und Anleger aufpassen.
Immer wieder kommt es vor, dass sich Online-Betrüg...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BaFin verhängt vermehrt Millionen-Bußgelder</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439850958&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 23.10.2024 jsc Frankfurt – Millionen-Bußgelder sind keine Ausnahme mehr: Allein in diesem Jahr erhielten N26, Solaris, C24 und Commerzbank einen jeweils siebenstelligen Bescheid. Die Aufsicht stellte hier wie dort einen Mangel in der Prävention von Geldwäsche fest. Die Verstöße liege...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>