<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Amundi, EDF Among Firms Asking EU Not to Water Down ESG Rules</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454181163&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Some of France’s largest companies, including Amundi SA and Electricite de France SA, have signed a letter to European policymakers urging them to ensure the bloc sticks with its current timetable for implementing ESG reporting rules.
The companies are responding to a growing wave of ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock to Cut About 1% of Its Employees, Staff Memo Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454181156&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. told employees it’s cutting roughly 1% of its workforce after it committed more than $25 billion for acquisitions last year to expand its reach in private-market assets and data.
The cuts are part of BlackRock’s efforts to realign its resources with the firm’s strategy,...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Plunging UK Markets Offer Fresh Warning Over Economy and Pile Pressure on Starmer</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454181154&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Plunging UK markets are serving a fresh warning about the British economy and heaping pressure on Keir Starmer’s embattled Labour government.
While UK bond yields have been creeping higher in recent months, anxiety in markets kicked into overdrive this week, with long-simmering worrie...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Should Keep Easing to Reach Neutral by Summer, Villeroy Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454181151&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should keep lowering borrowing costs at every meeting as long as the retreat in inflation matches its projections, according to Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau.
Cuts should continue until the deposit rate — currently 3% — reaches a level ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Amundi’s Bond Chief Says US 10-Year Yield Can Exceed 5% Again</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454148194&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- There’s a “reasonable” chance that the yield on 10-year US Treasuries will again test the key level of 5%, said Amaury D’Orsay, head of fixed income at Amundi SA, Europe’s largest asset manager.
D’Orsay is among a growing chorus warning that bond market repricing may have further to g...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>„AMERICA FIRST“</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454178297&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>J.P. Morgan erwartet in Donald Trumps zweiter Amtszeit mehr Unsicherheit für Unternehmen. Höhere Zölle erhöhen die Kosten, führen zu Inflation und weiter hohen Zinsen. „Die Folge könnte eine Rezession sein“, warnt Chefanalystin Joyce Chang.
► Im Gespräch Seite 9...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Warum Union Investment an der Tesla-Aktie festhält</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454175194&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>capital.de</author>
<description>Es war kein guter Jahresauftakt für die Tesla-Aktie: Als der Elektroauto-Hersteller vergangene Woche für 2024 erstmals einen sinkenden Fahrzeugabsatz meldete, brach der Titel um rund sechs Prozent ein. Das war nicht nur ein Schlag für Tesla-Aktionäre, sondern auch für all diejenigen, die in den Indu...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Szenaro bewahrheitet sich – Bafin stellt Insolvenzantrag für Element</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454182262&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>Die Bundesanstalt für Finanzdienstleistungsaufsicht (Bafin) hat einen Insolvenzantrag für das Insurtech Element gestellt. Das geht aus einem heute Mittag veröffentlichten Beschluss des Amtsgerichts Berlin-Charlottenburg hervor (Az. 36e IN 8660/24).
Auf Nachfrage von DAS INVESTMENT bestätigte die Auf...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dora: Zu diesem Termin müssen Finanzdienstleister die IKT-Register vorlegen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454166432&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>Die Uhr tickt für Deutschlands Finanzunternehmen: Am 17. Januar wird die europäische Dora-Verordnung wirksam. So weit, so bekannt. Jetzt hat die Bafin einen weiteren Termin verkündet: Bis zum 11. April 2025 sollen alle Dora-Verpflichteten ihre Informationsregister bei der Behörde einreichen.
Dora zi...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>J.P. Morgan beendet Hybrid-Arbeit – Mitarbeiter müssen wieder täglich ins Büro</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2454150018&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>Die US-Großbank J.P. Morgan Chase führt die vollständige Büropflicht wieder ein. Das Finanzinstitut verlangt von seinen mehr als 300.000 Mitarbeitern weltweit künftig eine Präsenz von fünf Tagen pro Woche. Diese Entscheidung bedeutet das Ende des bisherigen Hybrid-Modells, wie mit der Angelegenheit ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>