<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Die neuen Regeln für die UBS sind der Preis der Swissness</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3268941538097917154</link>
<author>handelszeitung.ch</author>
<description>Der Streit um neue Eigenkapitalvorschriften für die UBS geht weiter. Die Vorgaben sind hart, doch bekommt die Bank genug Anpassungszeit.

Holger Alich
Nun ist die Katze aus dem Sack: Am Freitag hat Finanzministerin Karin Keller-Sutter ihr Reformpaket für die Bankenregulierung vorgelegt. Kernstück is...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS-Finanzchef sieht Belastungen durch schwachen Dollar</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14213751854854733091</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Die UBS rechnet im Kerngeschäft Vermögensverwaltung mit Gegenwind durch die Währungsentwicklung.

«Im Grossen und Ganzen sind wir wirklich zufrieden mit den Fortschritten, die wir in allen unseren Geschäftsbereichen machen», sagte UBS-Finanzchef Todd Tuckner am Mittwoch auf einer Investorenkonferenz...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS-Vermögensstrategin: «Die US-Aktienrallye wird wahrscheinlich verpuffen»</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17071632477066255911</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Nach dem Zollschock heben Analysten die Gewinnschätzungen an. Dennoch bleibt die Lage unbeständig.

Laut Anthi Tsouvali, Strategin bei UBS Global Wealth Management, ist die Erholung der US-Aktien angesichts der Unsicherheiten im Zusammenhang mit den Zöllen das Beste, was in diesem Jahr passieren kan...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Die Rechtsschutzversicherer mit den meisten BaFin-Beschwerden</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4607082062527431608</link>
<author>procontra-online.de</author>
<description>Auch in der Rechtsschutzsparte gab es 2024 mehr Ärger zwischen Kunden und ihren Versicherern. Doch im Vergleich zur Kfz-Versicherung gab es deutlich weniger Anbieter mit hohen Beschwerdequoten., Im vergangenen Jahr hatte die BaFin deutlich mehr Beschwerden über private Krankenversicherer auf dem Tis...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Worauf sollte ich beim Renten-Abschlagsausgleich achten?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7344933792586701091</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Unser Leser, 57, will zusätzliche Beiträge bei der gesetzlichen Rente einzahlen, in Vorbereitung einer Frührente. Doch das Verfahren wirft Fragen auf.

WiWoWiWo Coach ist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnenten. Top-Experten beantworten hier all Ihre Fragen rund um Geldanlage, Vorsorge, K...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wie bauen Sie sich ein passives Einkommen in 2025 auf?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7477645262087056751</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Aus dem Handelsblatt-Archiv: Für ein passives Einkommen neben dem Job können Sie ihr Fachwissen nutzen. Finanzexperten erklären, mit welchen Praktiken so tatsächlich ein Nebenverdienst gelingt – und welche als unseriös gelten.

Um neben dem Job zusätzlich passives Einkommen zu generieren, sind Aktie...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>„Ein bisschen weniger Protzerei würde uns allen guttun"</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15549231481479162531</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>26 Jahre unabhängig, 150.000 Mark abgelehnt: Sven Putfarken spricht über Finanzplanung als Lebensplanung – und warum er mehr Bescheidenheit im Finanzsektor fordert.

Sven Putfarken, stellvertretender Vorsitzender des Network Financial Planner (IFNP), hat klare Vorstellungen davon, wie qualitativ hoc...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Lane Says June Cut Helps Keep Price Undershoot Temporary</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4776237539382120984</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank’s latest reduction in borrowing costs will guard against inflation getting stuck below 2%, according to Chief Economist Philip Lane.
Consumer-price gains are currently just below that target and are forecast by the ECB to slide further into 2026, before rebou...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB to Speed Up Reviews of Share Buyback Plans by European Banks</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15622544566223715748</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European banks’ wait time for regulatory approvals for their shareholder payout plans is about to get shorter, as the region’s top watchdog steps up efforts to boost efficiency.
The European Central Bank is making procedures “quicker and more risk-based, including through the use of d...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Expects Gradual Rule Change on Swiss Deferred Tax Assets</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3258152033016445381</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Newly-proposed rules on how to value deferred tax assets will likely be introduced gradually, UBS Group AG Chief Financial Officer Todd Tuckner said, in a step that would delay their impact on the bank’s capital requirements.
“It is reasonable to assume that there will be a phase-in p...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Wage Tracker Signals Pay Growth Will Plunge This Year</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3015645432804128623</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Wage growth in the euro zone will slow sharply in 2025, according to the European Central Bank’s main gauge of future pay increases – bolstering arguments that inflation is under control.
The ECB’s wage tracker, published Wednesday, predicts salaries will rise by an annual 1.7% in the...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Says Some Fine-Tuning Rate Cuts ‘Quite Likely’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17649893894240952727</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Martins Kazaks said further interest-rate cuts may be needed, according to Econostream Media.
“We’ve done a lot in terms of rate cuts, and monetary policy will need to remain vigilant to ensure that inflation stays around 2%,” he was cite...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Reeves Vows Record Health Boost as She Turns On Spending Tap</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15123902180145513433</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Chancellor of the Exchequer Rachel Reeves announced a record funding boost for the National Health Service in a spending review that marks a watershed moment for the Labour government after nearly a year in power focused on fiscal prudence.
The NHS will see a 3% real terms rise in day...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Publicis Groupe SA : BlackRock,[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2206988859533294894</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Publicis Groupe SA : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,47% du capital et 4,99% des droits de vote (28/05...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BNP Paribas Personal Finance veut doubler sa pro|tabilité en trois ans</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7192572272330824057</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Franck Joselin

La banque a présenté le plan stratégique à horizon 2028 de ses activités de crédit à la consommation. Elle compte profiter de la restructuration menée depuis trois ans pour prendre de nouvelles parts de marché.

Les voyants sont au vert pour les activités de BNP Paribas

Personal Fin...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubis : UBS Group AG[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9288153514491492499</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Rubis : UBS Group AG a franchi en baisse, directement et indirectement, par l'intermédiaire des sociétés qu'elle contrÎle, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 0,002% du capital et des droits de vote (05/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrefour : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13362780252624414</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Carrefour : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,64% du capital et 4,68% des droits de vote (06/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Abivax : J.P. Morgan Chase [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2378710391269297959</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Abivax : J.P. Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient, indirectement par l'intermédiaire des sociétés J.P.

Morgan Prime Inc., J.P. Morgan Securities plc et J.P. Morgan Securities LLC qu'elle contrÎle, 5,85% du capital e...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15366593451896178148</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>C le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,01% du capital et 4,00% des droits de vote (10/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3173374739717608745</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,20% du capital et 4,46% des droits de vote (10/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>DBV Technologies : JP Morgan[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8214741843673159608</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>DBV Technologies : JP Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient indirectement, par l'intermédiaire des sociétés qu'elle contrÎle, 4,17% du capital et des droits de vote (10/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Valeo : UBS Group AG[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6566842535640955034</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Valeo : UBS Group AG a franchi en baisse, indirectement, par l'intermédiaire des sociétés qu'elle contrÎle, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 0,32% du capital et 0,29% des droits de vote (06/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Verallia : JP Morgan Chase [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8948608990171836651</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Verallia : JP Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,66% du capital et 4,76% des droits de vote (28/05/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bureau Veritas : BlackRock, agissant[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5814663891221114143</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Bureau Veritas : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 6,59% du capital et 5,12% des droits de vote (10/06/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Covivio HÎtels : BNP Paribas [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16047880173751847458</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Covivio HÎtels : BNP Paribas a franchi en hausse, indirectement par l'intermédiaire des sociétés Cardif Assurance Vie et Cardif Retraite qu'elle contrÎle, le seuil de 10% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 10,84% du capital et des droits de vote (27/05/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Can Wait Until September to Even Discuss Next Rate Move, Vujcic Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17401376429207214962</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should wait until at least September to have an in-depth discussion about an interest-rate move, according to Governing Council member Boris Vujcic.
“We feel that we are now in a very good position,” the Croatian central-bank chief told Bloomberg Television. ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock, Goldman Scale Up Tax Trades in $3 Trillion SMA Boom</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12284462506601938150</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- This year’s stock market turbulence has punished ordinary investors. But for the wealthy, it’s opened up fresh opportunities to convert equity swings into tax breaks — fueling a growing Wall Street business that turns volatility into a financial advantage. 
BlackRock Inc., Goldman Sac...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Declines as Analysts Warn Capital Rules to Hurt Buybacks</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15490423976863103832</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG fell the most in two months as analyst warned that new capital demands imposed by Switzerland could crimp the bank’s competitiveness and its ability to make investor payouts. 
Shares of the wealth manager declined as much as 7.4% on Tuesday, more than reversing gains from...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>