<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Fidelity Fund That Rode China’s Epic Rally Is Back Buying Stocks</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445147908&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- After successfully riding China’s epic stock rally in late September, Fidelity International’s George Efstathopoulos is boosting positions again on expectations that fiscal stimulus will prop up the economy. 
The Singapore-based money manager, who oversees about $3 billion across asse...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Vujcic Says Risk of Undershooting Inflation Goal Has Risen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445023476&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The danger that the European Central Bank will fall short of its 2% inflation goal has risen, according to Governing Council member Boris Vujcic.
“Certainly the risk of undershooting the target has now increased compared to six months ago,” Vujcic told an event Monday in London.
At it...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Seeks Expanded US Banking License in Growth Push</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445013791&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS is seeking a wider permission to operate in the United States, a market it has earmarked for growth.  
The Swiss bank is considering applying for a license under the supervision of the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency, according to a spokesperson, who confirmed a Handelsb...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock, Block Fund Major Sustainable Aviation Fuel Deal</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445000743&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Sustainable aviation fuel is getting a huge boost from some of the world’s biggest companies. 
BlackRock Inc., Block Inc., Samsara Inc. and Ripple are participating in the Sustainable Aviation Buyers Alliance and buying certificates as part of the group’s $200 million in clean jet fue...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wall Street Teams With BlackRock to Provide Bond Price Data</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445000728&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Some of Wall Street’s biggest banks are teaming up with BlackRock Inc.’s Aladdin technology system to provide real-time pricing data for trading US corporate bonds – still one of the most opaque areas in financial markets.
It’s another step toward transparency in a market where hyper-...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Quarter-Point December Cut a Done Deal, Stournaras Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445000721&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is almost certain to cut interest rates by a quarter point in December, according to Governing Council member Yannis Stournaras.
Asked if such a move is a done deal, the Greek central bank chief said “more or less,” and that he thinks “25 basis points is an o...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Feeds Rising ETF Demand With First Mutual-Fund Flip</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2445000720&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. is feeding the beast: investors who have more of an appetite for ETFs than mutual funds.
The world’s biggest asset manager has converted the BlackRock International Dividend mutual fund into an ETF, after revealing plans in April to change its structure. The $765 millio...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Makhlouf Backs Prudent and Cautious Approach to Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2444990701&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Gabriel Makhlouf said there’s no rush to lower interest rates at a faster pace, rejecting the idea of bigger cuts.
“I am still a believer in a prudent and cautious approach,” the Irish official said Monday. “When the policy is working, we...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Stournaras Warns Trump Levies May Trigger Europe Recession</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2444990691&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) --
Europe will see economic activity weaken if the US imposes tariffs, according to European Central Bank Governing Council member Yannis Stournaras. 
“If I can advise our friends in the United States, this is my advice: don’t do it,” Stournaras, who heads Bank of Greece, said at Bloombe...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Nagel Warns Economic Fragmentation Risk Is Escalating</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2444981838&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Joachim Nagel sees the threat of a further fragmentation of the global economy, which could present central banks with new challenges in the form of higher or more volatile inflation.
“The first signs of geoeconomic fragmentation are beco...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>