<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Berlin nutzt Ausweichklausel von EU-Schuldenregeln</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18390687268219827240</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Mehr Spielraum zur Finanzierung von Rüstungsinvestitionen

fed Frankfurt –
Die Bundesregierung macht von der Möglichkeit Gebrauch, dass Ausgaben für Rüstung und Verteidigung nicht bei der Berechnung von Defizit und Schulden im Zuge der haushaltspolitischen Überwachung der EU berücksichtigt werden so...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Union Investment will mit Private Markets wachsen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4839640426721820797</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Neue Fonds für private und institutionelle Investoren

Bloomberg Frankfurt – Union Investment will im Bereich Private Markets wachsen und plant die Auflage von neuen Fonds. Schon jetzt verwaltet die DZ-Bank-Tochter in derartigen Anlagen mehrere Milliarden Euro. Der Fokus liegt auf Infrastruktur und ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wird der MSCI World zum Problemfall?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8666841338136328081</link>
<author>Cash.Online</author>
<description>Gerade für unerfahrene Kleinanleger gilt der MSCI World als der Welt-Aktienindex schlechthin. Doch das Blatt hat sich jüngst gewendet.

Insbesondere die großen Fonds und Pensionskassen haben schnell auf die erratische Zollpolitik von US-Präsident Donald Trump reagiert und Geld aus Amerika abgezogen...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>KI: Chancen im gesamten Innovationszyklus</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=1748082220435676207</link>
<author>Cash.Online</author>
<description>Der Zyklus in Bezug auf die Künstliche Intelligenz (KI) befindet sich sowohl aus technologischer als auch in Bezug auf Investitionen noch in den Kinderschuhen. Aus technologischer Sicht wird die schiere Geschwindigkeit der Effizienzsteigerungen zu einer schnelleren Produktinnovation und einer steige...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB to Mull Rate Hike by End of Year, Franklin Templeton Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12002486586267882906</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
The European Central Bank will pivot to start considering an interest-rate hike by the end of this year, according to Franklin Templeton, as the region’s defense spending is likely to heat up the economy.
“If you look out ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lagarde Isn’t Winning Over Disgruntled ECB Staff in Union Survey</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12016306783742898088</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde is struggling to win over staff who say they have little faith in the institution’s top management.
A majority of respondents in a new survey by labor union IPSO said it has little or no trust in the ECB’s Executive Board, especially t...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Rehn Sees Downside Risks to March Inflation Forecasts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4606381211710860791</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Olli Rehn said there’s a danger that inflation will dip below the 2% target due to the fallout from US trade levies, reiterating that this would be grounds to further lower interest rates.
“Financial markets seem to think that tariffs and...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro Rally Catches Bessent’s Eye as Bets for ECB Rate Cuts Grow</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16975710126783015762</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The euro’s rally is getting the attention of officials on both sides of the Atlantic, fueling expectations for deeper interest-rate reductions by the European Central Bank as the gains show little sign of slowing.
JPMorgan Chase & Co., BNP Paribas SA and Danske Bank A/S predict one eu...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Still Has a Gradual Margin for Rate Cuts, Villeroy Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16622319287746034937</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank has room to lower borrowing costs, according to Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau.
The trade war triggered by US tariffs will weigh on the global economy but won’t  not affect the inflation trend in Europe, he told Radio RTL on Monday.
- “T...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Guindos Warns of Disorderly Market Risk Amid Trade Turmoil</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5725370800623226731</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Vice President Luis de Guindos said that volatile financial markets must be watched closely amid the risk of declines spiraling out of control.
Speaking to European Parliament lawmakers in Brussels on Monday, he warned that despite a resilient banking system in t...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Prepares for June Cut With Tariffs Expected to Hurt Economy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16373112152060140716</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
European Central Bank officials are preparing to lower interest rates further, expecting lasting damage to the economy from US tariffs even if Donald Trump’s administration softens its stance in the weeks ahead.
Following ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>AI Startup Nscale Chases ByteDance Deal and $1.8 Billion in Debt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18422340647160982470</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Nscale, a startup that is less than a year old, is already trying to raise about $2.7 billion to build artificial intelligence infrastructure on the back of a pending partnership with ByteDance Ltd., the Chinese owner of TikTok, according to an offering document seen by Bloomberg.
The...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fiscal Support Since Pandemic Still Boosting Inflation, ECB Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8384005504635258383</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Aid measures by euro-zone governments during the pandemic and the war in Ukraine will keep stoking inflation in the years ahead, the European Central Bank said.
The increased spending will boost price growth by 0.7 percentage point this year, 0.4 percentage point in 2026 and 0.3 perce...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Union Investment sieht Wachstum in Private Markets, plant neue Fonds</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8371674414499043748</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (German)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Union Investment will im Bereich Private Markets wachsen und plant die Auflage von neuen Fonds. Schon jetzt verwaltet die DZ-Bank-Tochter in derartigen Anlage-Strategien mehrere Milliarden Euro. Das Kapital kommt von institutionellen und seit kurzem auch von privaten Kunden. Der Fokus...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS, Swiss Re und Co: Analyst setzt bei UBS, Swiss Re und Co den Rotstift an</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7583097734333666377</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Der cash Insider kommentiert die wichtigsten Börsenereignisse. Diese Woche: Eine Welle an Kurszielreduktionen, Zahlen von Roche und Nestlé wenig überzeugend. Und: Gegenangebot für Baloise nun vom Tisch?

cash Insider
Der cash Insider berichtet auch im Insider Briefing jeweils vorbörslich von brandak...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS, Swiss Re und Co: Analyst setzt bei UBS, Swiss Re und Co den Rotstift an</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12323007487417554085</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>In den Handelsräumen eines Londoner Finanzwertespezialisten laufen gleich gegen mehrere Schweizer Aktien grössere Wetten. Angeblich ist auch die UBS Ziel der Leerverkäufer. Und: Öffentliche «Lobhudelei» an die Adresse von Roche.

cash Insider
Der cash Insider berichtet auch im Insider Briefing jewei...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Publicis Groupe SA : BlackRock, [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=676509205131660949</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Publicis Groupe SA : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,46% du capital et 4,99% des droits de vote (25/04/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bureau Veritas : BlackRock, agissant[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2923876038867944881</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Bureau Veritas : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 6,09% du capital et 4,74% des droits de vote (22/04/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubis : UBS Group, a franchi en hausse, [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17957398329016008742</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Rubis : UBS Group, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 7,22% du capital et des droits de vote (17/04/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Veolia Environnement : Amundi, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4100458453390143959</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Veolia Environnement : Amundi, agissant pour le compte de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de et détient 4,98% du capital et des droits (07/04/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>DBV Technologies : JP Morgan Chase & Co a [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6377821672595168829</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>DBV Technologies : JP Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 7,72% du capital et des droits de vote (14/04/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Axa : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de[...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11473553192392276032</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Axa : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 6,02% du capital et 5,01% des droits de vote (11/04/25)....</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>So schützen Sie Ihr Vermögen im Fall eines Kriegs</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12814819871765537804</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Seit Russlands Überfall auf die Ukraine ist der Krieg zurück in Europa. Wie können Anleger zumindest ihr Vermögen für den Fall einer Ausweitung des Konflikts absichern?

Erstveröffentlichung: 2025-04-28 05:51:00 letzte Aktualisierung: 2025-04-28 05:53:05
WiWo Coachist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Patrick Kolb: „Es gibt attraktivere Sicherheitsinvestments als Rüstung“</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3708038406316139492</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>Er ist Mister Sicherheit bei UBS Asset Management – und das schon seit fast 20 Jahren: Patrick Kolb erklärt, weshalb ihm Rüstungsaktien trotz des Hypes nicht ins Portfolio kommen.

DAS INVESTMENT: Herr Kolb, ganz Europa spricht über Sicherheit. Neue Rüstungs-ETFs und -Fonds kommen auf den Markt und ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>