<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF Posts Record Outflow After Banner Year</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453340560&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Investors yanked a net $333 million from BlackRock Inc.’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF (IBIT) on Thursday, the most withdrawn from the record-breaking fund since its launch.
The fund also suffered a third consecutive day of outflows, its longest losing streak, according to data compiled ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Shares Rise as Exane Upgrades on Likely Buyback Increase</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453340553&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG shares rose the most in two months as analysts at BNP Paribas Exane recommended buying on expectations the Swiss lender will increase share buybacks.
The stock gained as much as 3.8% to be among the best performers in Europe on Friday, as Exane analysts including Jeremy S...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS Wealth Urges Chinese Stock Investors to Stay ‘Defensive’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453327030&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Chinese stock investors should “stay on the defensive side” as consumption remains weak and volatility is expected to rise with higher tariffs by Donald Trump on the horizon, according to UBS Global Wealth Management.
Investors should seek out stocks that “offer decent dividend yields...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Krypto-ETFs auf dem Vormarsch: Anbieter im Wettbewerb um den nächsten «heissen» Fonds</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453352582&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Gegen Ende des Jahres 2024 wurden bei der US-Börsenaufsichtsbehörde Papiere für eine Fülle neuartiger Angebote eingereicht. Zu den vorgeschlagenen Produkten gehörte ein ETF von ProShares, der die Rendite des S&P 500 in Bitcoin abbilden würde.
Die von Strive Asset Management und REX Shares geplanten ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Verkehrsinfrastruktur: Was ist realistisch, was nicht?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453376803&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung</author>
<description>Doppelt so viel Geld für die Schiene wie für die Straße, Sanierung vor Neubau – das ist neben dem Deutschlandticket der zentrale verkehrspolitische Erfolg der vergangenen drei Jahre. So wichtig diese Weichenstellung war, sie ist nur der Anfang eines gigantischen Sanierungsprogramms, mit dem wir in g...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wer soll das bezahlen?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453376807&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung</author>
<description>Nach der Sanierung der Riedbahn ist vor der nächsten Etappe der Generalsanierung. Wobei der Fokus auf die viel befahrene Bahnstrecke wohl etwas zu eng gezogen ist.
Es ließen sich noch die Carolabrücke in Dresden und die Rahmede-Talbrücke im Sauerland ergänzen, um das Ausmaß maroder Infrastruktur in ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Getlink SE : BlackRock, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453329583&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Getlink SE : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 4,99% du capital et 3,50% des droits de vote (20/12/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Société Générale : BlackRock, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453329523&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Société Générale : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,41% du capital et 4,88% des droits de vote (27/12/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rubis : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453329508&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Rubis : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 5,01% du capital et des droits de vote (20/12/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Safran : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2453329499&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Safran : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 4,94% du capital et 3,89% des droits de vote (27/12/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>