<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Fondsvermögen zurück auf Rekordniveau</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437327091&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Das erste Halbjahr 2024 war für die Finanzmärkte ein Zeitraum großer Ungewissheit: Geopolitische Spannungen, Zinspolitik, Börsengänge sowie Fusionen prägten das Geschehen und sorgten für viel Bewegung an den Börsen. Dennoch schienen DAX und andere Indizes weitgehend gefestigt zu sein. Anleger vertra...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Der neue ELTIF bietet Potenzial – auch für Vermittler</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437327098&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Die 2024 in Kraft getretene Novelle des European Long Term Investment Fund (ELTIF) eröffnet Privatanlegern die Chance, an der Wertentwicklung von Privatmarktanlagen teilzuhaben und ihr Portfolio sinnvoll zu diversifizieren. Im Gespräch mit Kunden sind Aufklärung und Wissensvermittlung gefragt. Für F...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Micro-Living: Investment mit Potenzial</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437327108&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Micro-Living ist ein Wohnkonzept, das zwischen Wohnungsmarkt und klassischem Beherbergungsgewerbe angesiedelt ist. Zu den bekanntesten Micro-Living-Formen zählen studentisches Wohnen, Service-Wohnen, Co-Living und zum Teil auch Senior Living. Ihr gemeinsames Merkmal ist, dass kompakte und voll ausge...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BaFin kritisiert Lebensversicherer: Kundennutzen nicht im Fokus</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437327185&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Die BaFin zeigt sich weiterhin ziemlich unzufrieden mit den Lebensversicherern in Bezug auf das Merkblatt zu den Wohlverhaltenspflichten. Insbesondere kritisiert die Aufsichtsbehörde, dass der Kundennutzen bei vielen Produkten nicht im Vordergrund stehe. Denn 13 Lebensversicherer wurden einer nähere...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ist der Versicherungsmakler noch unabhängig? Eine Einordnung auf Basis aktueller Gerichtsurteile</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437327187&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>AssCompact</author>
<description>Das Landgericht (LG) Bremen hatte über einen Fall (vgl. LG Bremen vom 11.07.2023, Az. 9 O 1081/22) zu entscheiden, bei dem ein Versicherungsmakler auf seiner Website als Anlageberater, Versicherungsmakler mit Erlaubnis nach §§ 34c, 34d und 34f Gewerbeordnung (GewO) sowie dem Angebot bundesweiter und...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Etsy CFO Taps Into AI to Perk Up Users With ‘Depressed’ Finances</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437448337&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Faced with an uncertain economic outlook, Etsy Inc. is looking for new ways to get its more than 95 million active users to spend. The online marketplace’s chief financial officer is counting on help from artificial intelligence and the cloud.
“People’s balance sheets are starting to ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Is Among Suitors Exploring Purchase of Credit Firm HPS</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437346956&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. is among firms exploring a purchase of HPS Investment Partners, according to people with knowledge of the matter, in a deal that would push the world’s biggest asset manager into the top ranks of the private-credit market.
The two firms have held talks as HPS also pursu...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Wunsch Warns on Rapid Cuts, Undecided on October: L’Echo</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437322656&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Pierre Wunsch cautioned against interest rates being lowered too quickly and said he’s undecided on a widely expected cut this month, according to Belgium’s L’Echo.
Trends in the euro-zone economy and inflation “motivate measured and prud...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Rates Can Be Neutral in 2025 If Inflation at 2%, Kazaks Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437316082&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Martins Kazaks said interest rates can be lowered next year to levels that neither stimulate nor restrict the economy — should inflation meet the 2% target.
The remarks are among the first from an ECB policymaker on where borrowing costs ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Germany Said to Tap Citi, Deutsche Bank, UBS for Uniper Deal</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437309987&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Germany’s government has selected banks to arrange a potential selldown of power company Uniper SE, which could rank among the country’s biggest share sales in recent years, according to people familiar with the matter.
Citigroup Inc., Deutsche Bank AG and UBS Group AG have been appoi...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>