<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Trockene Phasen und Starkregen im Wechsel</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9053011056003711364</link>
<author>Frankfurter Rundschau Deutschlandausgabe</author>
<description>In Deutschland kommt künftig laut Prognosen weiter dieselbe Wassermenge herunter – allerdings kann wegen der Extreme wohl weniger genutzt werden / Von Jörg Staude

Nach dem Regen kommt die Sonne und nach der Sonne der Regen. Mit derartigen Voraussagen beeindruckte schon der berühmte Seher die widers...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>EU-Partner gefährden Merz’ Milliardenplan</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5037920429930607347</link>
<author>Handelsblatt</author>
<description>Das Milliardenpaket von Union und SPD droht an EU-Defizitvorgaben zu scheitern. Denn viele Mitgliedstaaten denken nicht dran, diese zu ändern.

Es ist Anfang März, eine reguläre Sitzung der 27 EU-Botschafter. Der deutsche Vertreter, Michael Clauß, macht einen Vorstoß, über den sich fast alle anderen...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Urges Cautious Steps Even as Growth Outlook Worsens</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2434280483173775237</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
The European Central Bank should only lower interest rates into accommodative territory if the growth outlook deteriorates much further, according to Governing Council member Martins Kazaks. 
While US tariff policies may s...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Sees Inflation Job Almost Done Despite Tariff Mess</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16849893299937724837</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
European Central Bank officials are starting to open up on what monetary-policy remedies the region’s economy may need to cope with the recent jolts to global trade.
While US tariff fears top the agenda for attendees at th...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Prepares for June Cut as Economy Hurt Even If Trade Is Fixed</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14499537924751194036</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
European Central Bank officials are preparing to lower interest rates further, expecting lasting damage to the economy from US tariffs even if Donald Trump’s administration softens its stance in the weeks ahead.
Following ...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Centeno Says Uncertainty Is Dominating Economic Analysis</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10556377953006286763</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Subscribe to Economics Daily for the latest news and analysis.
European Central Bank Governing Council member Mario Centeno said economic analysis is currently dominated by “uncertainty” created largely by US trade policy, Jornal de Negocios reported, citing an interview. 
Recent deci...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Der Chef stellt sich gegen die Auszeit. Was tun?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12865031533124202588</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Gerne würde unsere Leserin sechs Monate verreisen. Doch ihr Chef verwehrt ihr das Sabbatical. Welche Möglichkeiten hat sie?

Erstveröffentlichung: 2025-04-27 12:48:03 letzte Aktualisierung: 2025-04-27 12:48:03
WiWo Coachist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnenten. Top-Experten beantworten...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>