<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Lane Says Return to 2% Inflation Target Not Yet Secure</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428609885&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank’s battle to return inflation to 2% isn’t won and interest rates must stay as high as necessary to achieve that goal, without harming the economy unduly, according to Chief Economist Philip Lane.
“The return to target is not yet secure,” Lane said Saturday. “I...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Holzmann Says September Cut Isn’t ‘Foregone Conclusion’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428596256&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Robert Holzmann warned that interest rates won’t necessarily be lowered next month — despite several of his colleagues signaling a cut.
“As always, I keep my reservations until the day of decision, and we’ll have a number of data coming i...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Gears Up for Next Interest Rate Cut With Inflation Slowing</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428596250&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank officials talking up the prospect of another reduction in interest rates next month will take heart from forecasts suggesting inflation is plummeting back toward their target.
Nine members of the ECB’s rate-setting Governing Council are attending the Federal Rese...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vorsicht, Buffett-Effekt: Darum ist es gefährlich, die Aktienkäufe des Starinvestors zu kopieren</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428596405&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Handelsblatt.com</author>
<description>Erstveröffentlichung: 2024-08-24 09:24:03 letzte Aktualisierung: 2024-08-24 09:31:30
Warren Buffett gilt als berühmtester noch lebender Großinvestor. Wenn der Chef des Beteiligungsunternehmens Berkshire Hathaway eine Aktie kauft, gilt das als Gütesiegel.
Viele Privatanleger und auch institutionelle ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Das droht beim Wegfall der Ehegatten-Steuerklassen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428598939&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Erstveröffentlichung: 2024-08-24 11:06:03 letzte Aktualisierung: 2024-08-24 11:06:05
WiWo Coach ist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnenten. Top-Experten beantworten hier all Ihre Fragen rund um Geldanlage, Vorsorge, Karriere, Steuern und Recht.
Die Frage: Laut einem Gesetzentwurf sollen ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>