<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Die USA wanken</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4387892375652738445</link>
<author>WELT AM SONNTAG</author>
<description>Bisher gilt Amerika als sicherer Hafen an den Börsen. Unter Donald Trump könnte sich das ändern

Die Warnungen mehren sich. Vor ein paar Tagen prophezeit Jamie Dimon wie die trojanische Schwarzseherin Kassandra das Unheil: „Sie werden einen Riss auf dem Anleihemarkt sehen, ok? Es wird passieren“, sa...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Le Conseil fédéral veut imposer plus de mesures à UBS</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2846122042717210129</link>
<author>handelszeitung.ch</author>
<description>L'UBS, banque d'importance systémique mondiale, se voit imposer des contraintes. La banque aux trois clés devra notamment détenir plus de fonds propres pour ses filiales étrangères. Le Conseil fédéral propose une «Lex UBS» pour protéger la Confédération, le contribuable et l'économie.

Schweizer Ver...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wirtschaftsrechtlerin «Leisten kann sich die UBS die Kosten allemal»</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16726722205277089844</link>
<author>tagesanzeiger.ch</author>
<description>Corinne Zellweger-Gutknecht erklärt, was das grössere Kapitalpolster für die Grossbank bedeutet. Und warum der Staat und die Steuerzahler dennoch nicht aus dem Schneider sind.

Die Grossbank UBS hat die letzten Monate so massiv gegen eine höhere Eigenkapitalunterlegung der Auslandstöchter lobbyiert,...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Vujcic Says Interest-Rate Reductions Are Nearly Done</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12874734544369090548</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) --
The European Central Bank’s interest-rate cutting campaign is almost over, Governing Council member Boris Vujcic said.
“I would agree that we are nearly done,” the Croatian central-bank chief told reporters on the sidelines of the 31. Dubrovnik Economic Conference. “If our projections...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Charting the Global Economy: ECB Nearing End of Rate-Cut Cycle</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15555406917346947804</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) --
The European Central Bank is nearing the end of its campaign to lower interest rates after its eighth reduction in a year, according to ECB President Christine Lagarde.
With the euro-zone economy suffering repeated blows from US tariffs, the deposit rate was lowered by a quarter-point...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Schnabel Says Now Is Right Time to Boost Role of Euro</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=371201979289145328</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) --
European Central Bank Executive Board member Isabel Schnabel sees a favorable moment now to strengthen euro’s global role as investors turn to Europe.
There’s a “window of opportunity” to increase the international role of the euro, she said in a question to a panel at the 31st Dubrov...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Don’t Count on a Sustained Fed-ECB Decoupling, Schnabel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8767996883933399897</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) --
It would be wrong to expect a persistent policy divergence between the US Federal Reserve and the European Central Bank, according to Executive Board member Isabel Schnabel.
“I expect this trade conflict to play out as a global shock that’s working for both global demand and supply — ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Is in Good Position on Rates, Lagarde Tells Monaco Info</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8188294519983336364</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The latest interest-rate moves primes the European Central Bank to meet its medium-term inflation goal, President Christine Lagarde told television station Monaco Info.
“We think we have really reached a good position,” she said in an interview broadcast Saturday, adding that the late...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>