<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>Die KI zieht in die Amtsstuben ein</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17158495511482380861</link>
<author>Kronen Zeitung</author>
<description>Künstliche Intelligenz dringt immer tiefer in alle Lebensbereiche der Menschen ein
Auf der Suche nach Steuereinnahmen für die Budgetsanierung hat das Finanzministerium die künstliche Intelligenz entdeckt. Durch Steuerhinterziehung entgehen dem Staat jedes Jahr bis zu 15 Milliarden Euro! Um sich zumi...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>J.P. Morgan ist das Maß – aber auch das richtige?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11225425456356015276</link>
<author>FAZ.NET</author>
<description>Die amerikanischen Großbanken spielen in einer anderen Liga als die europäischen. Allein J.P. Morgan (JPM) hat mit umgerechnet 25 Milliarden Euro im ersten Halbjahr mehr verdient als die drei profitabelsten Banken Europas – HSBC, Santander und BNP Paribas – zusammen. Europas Top Ten haben zwar in di...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB ‘Insurance Cut’ Not Needed With Inflation at 2%, Rehn Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=1731986010768114039</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is in no rush to lower interest rates further after inflation hit its 2% target and with the economy performing slightly better than thought, according to Governing Council member Olli Rehn. 
While policymakers must pay close attention to dangers that could w...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Lagarde Says Labor Market Has Weathered Recent Shocks Well</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2082083340943991559</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Europe’s labor market has proved surprisingly resilient in the face of a once-in-a-generation inflation shock and aggressive interest-rate hikes, according to European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde.
Employment expanded by 4.1% between the end of 2021 and mid-2025, nearly as...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>