<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Leans Toward October Cut But Warns Markets</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435914444&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is likely to lower borrowing costs at this month’s meeting and beyond, but some investors’ and economists’ easing expectations appear exaggerated, according to Governing Council member Martins Kazaks.
“We will discuss and decide when we meet next time and wil...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Fink Says Europe Needs Unified Banking Market</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435865877&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. Chief Executive Officer Larry Fink urged Europe to continue unifying its banking market, while stopping short of commenting on a potential combination of Commerzbank AG and UniCredit SpA.
“Europe needs a stronger capital markets system and it needs a more unified bankin...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Rehn Says Slowing Inflation Firms Case for October Cut</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435865874&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Easing inflation pressures and a deteriorating euro-zone economy support the case for an interest-rate cut this month, European Central Bank Governing Council member Olli Rehn said.
“We have received further confirmation from recent statistical data that inflation is slowing down,” th...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Fink Calls for Western Firms to Review China Ties</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435865861&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Western companies should be reassessing their ties to China in light of its support for the Russian economy, according to BlackRock Inc. Chief Executive Officer Larry Fink. 
“Ukraine is at our doorsteps here and I’m surprised that there’s not a larger questioning or demanding — you’re...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Fink Says Market Is Wrong on Fed Rate-Cut Bets</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435865849&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. Chief Executive Officer Larry Fink said the market is pricing too many interest-rate cuts from the Federal Reserve given the US economy continues to grow.
“I don’t see any landing,” Fink told Bloomberg Television’s Francine Lacqua in an interview Tuesday on the sideline...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro-Zone Inflation Drops Below 2%, Backing ECB Cut Bets</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435865841&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Euro-area inflation slowed below the European Central Bank’s 2% target for the first time since 2021 — backing investor bets that interest rates may be lowered more quickly than previously anticipated.
Consumer prices rose 1.8% from a year ago in September, down from 2.2% in the previ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock to Become Top SellerX Shareholder After Debt Deal</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435865839&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. is set to become the largest shareholder in SellerX as part of a deal to slash the former unicorn’s debt load, according to people familiar with the matter.  
BlackRock, an existing lender to the Berlin-based firm, will take a stake in the business as part of a debt-for...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Italy’s Meloni Discussed BlackRock Investments With CEO Fink</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435860849&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni discussed possible investments in the country by BlackRock Inc. with the US firm’s chief executive officer, Larry Fink.
The talks focused on strategic infrastructure such as data centers, as well energy and transport, according to a statement from...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Nagel Says ECB Bond Purchases to Be Limited to Exceptional Cases</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435860842&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Bundesbank President Joachim Nagel said that future purchases of government bonds by the European Central Bank should be reserved for special cases.
“The extensive bond purchases contributed to price stability in an era of low inflation, but they were also associated with numerous sid...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Im Bulgaria-Berufungsprozess nimmt UBS Platz der Credit Suisse ein</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2435854593&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>cash.ch</author>
<description>Die UBS versuchte vor kurzem, die Einstellung des Verfahrens gegen sie zu erreichen. Die Bank argumentierte, dass die Übernahme der Credit Suisse die gleichen Folgen haben sollte wie der Tod einer natürlichen Person in einem Verfahren. Mit anderen Worten, das Verschwinden der Nummer zwei der Bank-Br...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>