<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Fund Gives Up China Towers After Missing Loan</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461075214&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A BlackRock Inc. fund forfeited a Shanghai office complex to Standard Chartered Plc after it didn’t make a loan payment for the property, according to people familiar with the matter.  
A fund unit of the New York-based asset manager opted not to make a payment for a syndicated loan l...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bundesbank to Publish Proposal on Debt Brake After Election, Nagel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461025458&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Germany’s central bank will present a suggestion on how to overhaul the country’s strict borrowing limits after this month’s national ballot, Bundesbank President Joachim Nagel said.
“There’s room to maneuver to change the debt break,” he said in London on Wednesday. “We will come up ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Shouldn’t Cut Hastily as Rates Near Neutral, Nagel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461009636&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank mustn’t rush further interest-rate cuts, especially as borrowing costs approach a level that neither restricts nor stimulates the economy, Governing Council Joachim Nagel said.
“The closer we get to the neutral rate, the more appropriate it becomes to take a ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock, FDIC Seek to End Regulatory Row Over Bank Stakes</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461004124&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. and the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. are trying to resolve a months-long dispute over the asset manager’s stakes in US banks, according to people familiar with the matter.
Negotiations began before a Feb. 10 deadline for BlackRock to sign a so-called passivity agreem...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Elderson Says Data More Important Than Neutral for Policy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2460985346&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Executive Board member Frank Elderson said that incoming economic data is more important for setting monetary policy than the neutral rate of interest.
Echoing other ECB officials who also say neutral — a theoretical level than neither stimulates nor restricts ec...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Shouldn’t Cut by Half-Point This Year, Holzmann Tells CNBC</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2460975354&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank shouldn’t increase the size of its interest-rate cuts to perk up the region’s flagging economy, Governing Council member Robert Holzmann told CNBC.
Warning that US trade tariffs could yet revive price pressures, the hawkish Austrian official urged the ECB to ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ING folgt Deka, Citi, Universal Invest mit Frankfurt-Umzug</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2460996244&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (German)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- In der Frankfurter Finanzbranche hält der Trend zu Umzügen in modernere Büros an. Nach DekaBank, Citigroup und Universal Investment folgt nun auch die ING Deutschland.
Sie will 2028 mit ihrem Hauptsitz ins Hafenpark Quartier im Frankfurter Ostend ziehen, hieß es in einer Mitteilung.
M...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ärger für Trade Republic: BaFin schaltet sich ein – Tagesgeldzinsen betroffen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461007382&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Aktuell gibt es Ärger für den Neobroker Trade Republic. Dabei hat sich sogar die deutsche Finanzaufsicht Bafin eingeschaltet. Betroffen ist das beliebte Zinskonto des Berliner Fintechs. Das genau ist hier passiert und das sollten Kunden jetzt unbedingt wissen.
Trade Republic ist einer der beliebtest...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hagim verliert juristische Schlammschlacht gegen Private-Debt-Team</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461012240&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Der Fall hat in der Frankfurter Private-Debt-Szene hohe Wellen geschlagen: Ende 2023 wurde das komplette Corporate-Private-Debt-Team des Vermögensverwalters H&A Global Investment Management (Hagim) um dessen Leiter Richard Kuckelkorn von heute auf morgen vor die Tür gesetzt. Die Art und Weise, wie d...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>US-Zollpolitik trifft auch Siemens Energy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2461012277&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 13.2.2025
mic München
Die US-Zollpolitik wird auch Siemens Energy treffen. „Wir werden Effekte haben“, sagte Vorstandsvorsitzender Christian Bruch anlässlich der Vorlage der endgültigen Zahlen des ersten Quartals (31. Dezember). Jedoch könne man noch nicht quantifizieren, was dies ne...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>