<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>UBS Weighs Credit Suisse China Stake Swap With Beijing Government</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402238784&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG is in discussions to attain full ownership of its China platform by swapping its holding in Credit Suisse’s onshore securities venture with a Beijing government investment fund, according to people familiar with the matter.
The Zurich-based lender is proposing to buy the ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wealth Management’s Rising Star in Asia Has Tricky Task at UBS</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402238778&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Young Jin Yee quit her last job after less than six months to take on one of the hardest tasks in private banking: combining the Asia operations of UBS Group AG and Credit Suisse.
Now almost 10 months into her new role as UBS’s co-head of Asia-Pacific wealth management, the former int...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402294083&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi, en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,54% du capital et 4,45% des droits de vote (02/04/24).

...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Soitec : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402294082&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Soitec : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi, en baisse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 4,98% du capital et 3,90% des droits de vote (02/04/24).

...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Solocal : UBS Group a [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402294068&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Solocal : UBS Group a franchi en hausse, indirectement par l'intermédiaire de la société Credit Suisse Asset Management LLC qu'elle contrôle, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient 5,75% du capital et 5,73% des droits de vote (08/04/24).

...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Arkema : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402294061&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Arkema : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi, en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,01% du capital et 4,04% des droits de vote (08/04/24).

...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrefour : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402294060&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Carrefour : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi, en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 6,23% du capital et 4,97% des droits de vote (08/04/24).

...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Der letzte Fan der Ampel Wie Volker Wissing gegen die Krise der Koalition kämpft</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2402279439&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>tagesspiegel.de</author>
<description>Als der Mythos von der Fortschrittskoalition entstand, drückte Volker Wissing auf den Auslöser. Der damalige FDP-Generalsekretär schoss im September 2021, wenige Tage nach der Bundestagswahl, das berühmte Selfie mit seinem Parteichef Christian Lindner und den damaligen Grünenchefs Robert Habeck und ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>