<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Wunsch Says Talk of Half-Point Rate Cut Is ‘Premature’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440303277&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Pierre Wunsch said it’s far too early to start considering a half-point interest-rate reduction in December.
In an interview on Bloomberg Television’s “Balance of Power” on Thursday, the Belgian central-bank-chief said that while the euro...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Says FDIC Plan Would Hurt Investors, Cost Banks</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440303273&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. called on the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. to promptly withdraw proposed restrictions on money managers’ stakes in lenders, contending the rule change would upend index funds, make it more costly for banks to raise capital and disrupt the economy.
The proposal presen...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Would Need ‘Powerful’ Data for Big Rate Cuts, Makhlouf Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440293471&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should reserve big interest-rate cuts for exceptional circumstances, according to Governing Council member Gabriel Makhlouf, who said he prefers a “cautious” approach to ensure that inflation’s retreat to 2% stays on track.
“The data has to be very powerful f...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Best Policy Choice Is Measured Rate Cuts, Muller Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440293455&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should stick to lowering borrowing costs at a gradual and measured pace, Governing Council member Madis Muller said, pushing back against suggestions by some of his colleagues to consider bigger steps.
“With increased confidence in reaching our target it make...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Private Credit Firm Is Dragged Into Very Public Scrap With Union</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440288692&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Private credit firm Pemberton Asset Management has got into a scrap with an unlikely adversary — one of the UK’s largest trade unions. 
Unite the Union is protesting against the London-based credit specialist over its management of a maker of ready meals called Oscar Mayer, which Pemb...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ermotti Says UBS Is Thinking About What’s Next After Credit Suisse Merger</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440281790&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Eighteen months after its rescue takeover of rival Credit Suisse, UBS Group AG Chief Executive Officer Sergio Ermotti said his firm is starting to think about what comes next as technology advances sweep through the industry.
“We all know that our industry — like many other industries...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Kazaks Says All Options on Table for Interest Rates: CNBC</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440281789&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Martins Kazaks said officials will consider a range of options in the coming meetings — including standing pat and cutting interest rates in bigger steps. 
“Everything should be on the table,” the Latvian central-bank chief told CNBC on T...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Shouldn’t Rush With Interest-Rate Cuts, Nagel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440281768&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank shouldn’t hurry too much to lower borrowing costs but remain flexible, according to Governing Council member Joachim Nagel.
The Bundesbank president, who’s attending the International Monetary Fund annual meetings in Washington, said all options are on the ta...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Germany’s Economy Risks Period of Stagnation, Bundesbank Warns</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440272493&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Germany’s economy may end the year in stagnation after a shallow recession in the six months through September, according to the Bundesbank. 
Output probably fell “slightly” in the third quarter, after a 0.1% drop in the second, the central bank said Thursday in its monthly report. Gr...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Goldman, BNP See Credit’s Blanket Rally Turn to Cherry Picking</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440272485&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The era of a rising tide lifting all boats in the global credit market may be over.
Analysts at Goldman Sachs Group Inc. and BNP Paribas SA are forecasting the end of a rally that has turned the world’s credit market into a uniform mass of expensive assets. They recommend taking a mor...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>