<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>BlackRock’s Fink Calls Elevated Inflation World’s ‘Biggest Risk’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456891891&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. Chief Executive Officer Larry Fink said investors are too quick to conclude that high inflation is over, raising the prospect that bond yields will rise along with steeper prices.
“The biggest risk we have worldwide today is the world believes we are past the high point...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Impax CEO Says Sudden Loss of $6 Billion Mandate Is ‘a Blow’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456891885&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The chief executive officer of Impax Asset Management Group Plc says the sudden exit of one of its biggest clients represents a setback, as the firm embarks on a number of strategy adjustments to reverse a losing streak.
Impax is still recovering from a decision by St. James’s Place P...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Rate-Cutting Plans Survive First Contact With Trump’s Return</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456879000&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Plans by the European Central Bank to push ahead with interest-rate cuts are withstanding the early jolts in US economic policy driven by Donald Trump’s return to the White House.
Speaking during the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, officials including President Christine L...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Is Confident on Inflation Stabilizing at Target, Rehn Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456878996&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is confident inflation will stabilize at its 2% target and monetary policy will cease to be restrictive in the first half of this year, according to Governing Council member Olli Rehn.
The Finnish official said the ECB is vigilantly monitoring inflation, noti...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Germany Is Still Struggling to Exit Stagnation, Bundesbank Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456869565&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A meaningful recovery in Germany’s economy is unlikely at the moment, according to the Bundesbank.
After two years of shrinking output and next to no growth in recent quarters, the outlook for Europe’s largest economy remains clouded, the central bank said Wednesday in its monthly rep...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS CEO Warns Policymakers Not to Ignore Risk of High Debt Level</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456869555&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Policymakers trying to predict the next financial crisis should spend more time thinking about high levels of government debt than obscure market risks, Sergio Ermotti, Chief Executive Officer of UBS Group AG, told an audience at the World Economic Forum on Wednesday.  
“Maybe we shou...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Not Behind Curve and Will Cut Gradually, Lagarde Tells CNBC</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456860315&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank isn’t lowering interest rates too slowly and will maintain its measured approach to easing monetary policy, President Christine Lagarde told CNBC.
“We do not see ourselves behind the curve,” Lagarde said Wednesday in an interview in Davos, where she’s attendi...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Escriva Says Rate Cut Next Week Is ‘Most Likely’ Scenario</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456860293&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Jose Luis Escriva said another reduction in borrowing costs at next week’s meeting is very probable as recent data confirm the outlook for inflation.
“The market expects a further cut of 25 basis points,” the Spanish central-bank governor...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Stournaras Says Rates Should Come Close to 2% by End-2025</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456854292&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should continue to gradually cut interest rates, aiming to bring them to near 2% by year-end, Governing Council member Yannis Stournaras told Greece’s Naftemporiki newspaper. 
- Euro-area inflation continues to slow in line with forecasts and maybe even more,...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Knot Is Content With Market View on Next Two Meetings</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2456854291&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Klaas Knot said investor bets for interest-rate cuts in January and March are reasonable, while any commitment beyond is difficult due to heightened global uncertainty.
“I’m pretty comfortable with the market expectations for the upcoming...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>