<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Nagel Fears Slower Growth, Faster Inflation If Trump Wins</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437124697&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Europe’s economy could face significantly less growth and more inflation, should Donald Trump win re-election as US president, European Central Bank Governing Council member Joachim Nagel warned.
Victory for Trump “could be accompanied by drastic increases in tariffs, an expansionary ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Germany Said to Tap Citi, Deutsche Bank, UBS for Uniper Deal</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437119592&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Germany’s government has selected banks to arrange a potential selldown of power company Uniper SE, which could rank among the country’s biggest share sales in recent years, according to people familiar with the matter.
Citigroup Inc., Deutsche Bank AG and UBS Group AG have been appoi...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fidelity Set to Unveil a Revamped Desktop-Trading Platform</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437119586&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Fidelity Investments is unveiling a revamped desktop platform for active traders, featuring faster processing speeds and a refreshed look.
The firm’s Active Trader Pro platform, which will include a new engine powering behind-the-scenes processes, will be rolled out as a beta version ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Centeno Warns Against Big ECB Moves, Calls for ‘Gradualism’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437110188&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should avoid outsized moves in lowering interest rates, according to Governing Council member Mario Centeno.
“We have to be cautious — maintain gradualism in decisions,” the Portuguese official told reporters in Lisbon on Tuesday. “The most important word in ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>German Economy May Contract in 2024, Bundesbank Chief Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437110186&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The German economy is likely to experience another year of contraction with the US election posing an additional risk to Europe’s growth, according to Bundesbank President Joachim Nagel.
“This year we’re not expecting any growth at all, or possibly even a recession, because the second...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Private Credit Probe Finds Banks Don’t See Full Exposures</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437110162&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Europe’s banks don’t fully grasp how much they could get hit by turmoil in the burgeoning market for private credit, creating the need for more stringent disclosure rules, a top European Central Bank official said.
“We have recently completed a deep dive on the topic and found that ba...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Amundi Buys Polish Bonds as Investors Tilt Away From Hungary</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437093459&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Amundi SA has been buying Polish local-currency bonds as Europe’s biggest asset manager joins the ranks of investors who are reducing positions in Hungary.
The firm, which oversees $2.3 trillion in investments, is betting that Poland’s central bank will be slower to cut rates because ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>BlackRock, Tycoon-Backed YTL Set to Buy Singapore Serviced Apartments</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437093458&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. and the hotel unit of Malaysian developer YTL Corp. are set to purchase a group of serviced apartments in a prime office building in Singapore’s Central Business District, according to people familiar with the matter.
The world’s largest asset manager is seeking to buy ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Cut Next Week Wouldn’t Guarantee December Move, Vasle Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437093452&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Reducing interest rates in October wouldn’t mean that the European Central Bank is certain to do so again at its final meeting of the year, according to Governing Council member Bostjan Vasle.
“Even if the ECB happens to decide to lower rates next week, that wouldn’t automatically mea...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Nagel Says He’s Open to Consider October Rate Cut</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2437093450&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Bundesbank Chief Joachim Nagel said he’s willing to talk about an interest-rate cut at next week’s European Central Bank decision.
“I want to wait until the actual meeting, but I am certainly open to considering the possibility of taking another interest rate step,” he told the Table ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>