<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>GEFÄHRLICHE BLASENBILDUNG</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7489416296015862547</link>
<author>WELT AM SONNTAG</author>
<description>Noch verzeichnet die Karte zwischen den Orten Delhi und Rayville im US-Bundesstaat Louisiana nur die „Holly Ridge“-Grundschule, die „Holly Ridge“-Baptistenkirche und einen Gebrauchtwagenhändler – der Rest sind Reisfelder, Sumpfland und kleine Farmen mit großen Kornspeichern. Genau dort, mitten im lä...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Needs December Cut to Safely Reach 2% Inflation, Simkus Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14127976752781260926</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should ensure inflation and economic growth don’t disappoint by lowering interest rates again in December, according to Governing Council member Gediminas Simkus.
Without such a move, consumer-price gains risk falling short of the 2% target, the Lithuanian ce...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lagarde Says ECB Has Hit Inflation Goal But Uncertainty Remains</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16548923149757246968</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank has achieved its goal of taming prices but uncertainty persists over the outlook despite the trade deal with the US, President Christine Lagarde said.
“Interest rates have to target an inflation level, which we do target, and which we have now reached,” Lagar...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Scicluna Says ECB Can Cope With Downside Risks and Rate on Hold</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=696691649927718630</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank’s interest rates are “fine where they are,” even when considering downside risks to the economy and an inflation forecast slightly below the 2% target in 2027, Governing Council member Edward Scicluna said.
Policymakers will keep a careful eye on trade tensio...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB at ‘Good Equilibrium,’ No Need to Ease More, Stournaras Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11505755658100242029</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is probably done lowering borrowing costs, with any further easing needing meaningful changes to the outlook for prices and economic growth, Governing Council member Yannis Stournaras said.
While inflation is expected to be slightly below 2% in the coming yea...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Powell zwischen Inflation und Jobs: US-Geldpolitik auf Balanceakt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=1230999936218844148</link>
<author>FOCUS online</author>
<description>In Europa bleiben die Finanzmärkte in Bewegung: So musste Frankreich jüngst einen Rückschlag hinnehmen, als die Rating-Agentur Fitch das Kreditrating des Landes von AA- auf A+ herabstufte. Damit liegt Fitch nun unter den Bewertungen der anderen großen Rating-Agenturen. Als Gründe nannte Fitch das ge...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>KI-Fonds: Kurzfristig top, langfristig Durchschnitt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9175705255002488470</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>Die europäischeRatingagenturScope hat in einer Studie die Performance von Fonds mit Künstliche-Intelligenz-Bezug unter die Lupe genommen. Das Ergebnis: Der KI-Hype flacht ab – auch wenn die Dynamik der Technologie anhält.
Die Analyse unterscheidet zwischen zwei Fondstypen:
Fonds, die in KI-Unternehm...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>