<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>BlackRock Seeks Bigger Foothold in Crypto Derivatives Market</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439138713&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- BlackRock Inc. is pushing to have its money-market digital coin more widely used as collateral for crypto derivatives trades, as Wall Street firms push deeper into digital asset markets.
The world’s biggest asset manager and its brokerage partner, Securitize, are in early talks with s...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Rehn to Seek Another Term as Head of Finnish Central Bank</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439116798&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Olli Rehn is seeking a second seven-year term as the governor of Finland’s central bank.
“I have enough energy and motivation to continue working as the governor of the Bank of Finland, if I am elected, and to weigh in at the ECB Governin...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro-Zone Inflation Seen Just Below 2% in 2025, ECB Poll Shows</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439108910&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank will see inflation dip just below its target next year, according to its quarterly survey of professional forecasters.
Consumer prices will rise 1.9% in 2025, down from a previous forecast of 2%, a release on Friday showed. The projections for 2024 and 2026 w...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro Parity Threat Is Back on Trump Tariffs Risk, ECB Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439108907&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The risk of the euro sliding to parity with the dollar is mounting in financial markets after this week’s interest-rate cut and a stark reminder that a Donald Trump presidency could spark a global trade war.
Just days after Trump suggested US tariffs could be aimed at Europe as well a...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Villeroy Seeks Flexibility on Speed, Size of Rate Cuts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439104911&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank should remain flexible as it cuts interest rates in response to cooling inflation and a weakening economy, according to Governing Council member Francois Villeroy de Galhau.
Speaking less than a day after policymakers lowered borrowing costs for the third tim...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Black Workers in City of London Say Inclusion Is No Longer a Priority</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439099747&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Black professionals in the City are noticing a shift. At first it was subtle; fewer Black History Month events or a shrinking number of external speakers.
Then the changes became more apparent. Recruitment campaigns for underrepresented groups were abandoned while diversity, equity an...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Has Right Focus on Bank Risks a Decade On, Ex-Official Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439099741&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank is correct to be preparing lenders for threats that were difficult to imagine when it started regulating the industry 10 years ago, according to an official who help set up its oversight arm. 
The ECB’s work to make banks ready for risks including geopolitica...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Diese drei Geno-Banken schlüpfen unter Rettungsschirm: Überblick</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439108891&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (German)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Im genossenschaftlichen Bankensektor in Deutschland ist innerhalb kurzer Zeit ein drittes Institut auf Hilfe von der gruppeneigenen Sicherungseinrichtung angewiesen, wie in dieser Woche bekannt wurde. Sie springt immer dann ein, wenn Banken aus dem Sektor in Schwierigkeiten geraten. H...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Wissen die mehr? Blackrock, Microstrategy und Fidelity kaufen fleißig Bitcoin und Ethereum</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2439110581&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Wissen die etwas, was die anderen nicht wissen? Blackrock und Fidelity kaufen nämlich fleißig Bitcoin und Ethereum und Microstrategy gründet gleich eine ganze Krypto-Bank. Was Anleger jetzt wissen und tun sollten.
27 Millionen Dollar flossen in den vergangenen 3 Handelstagen in Ethereum-ETFs - die ü...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>DER JOKER FÜR DIE RENTE</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2438452025&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Capital</author>
<description>GELDANLAGE
Spezialisten für aktive Fonds
SAN FRANCISCO
Im Zentrum der KI-Revolution...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>