<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>UBS angezählt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440471634&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bilanz (Schweiz)</author>
<description>Es ist eine Titelstory, die wie aus einer anderen Welt erscheint: «Der Fall SBG», titelte BILANZ im November 1994 mit dem Anriss: «Von CS-Gut abgehängt, von BZ-Ebner umzingelt.» Die Schweizerische Bankgesellschaft, wie sich die heutige UBS in der deutschsprachigen Schweiz nannte, stand damals heftig...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Zwei Risikokapitalisten über die Chancen von Hydromea</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440471654&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bilanz (Schweiz)</author>
<description>„Enormes Potenzial”
«Hydromea will die Unterwasserinfrastruktur grundlegend verändern. Mit innovativen Technologien möchte das Unternehmen Arbeiten unter Wasser effizienter, sicherer und nachhaltiger machen. Neben Robotern und Tauchdrohnen hat Hydromea mit Luma eine kabellose Datenübertragungslösung...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lagarde to Hold Dinners With ECB Officials Before Most Meetings</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440519811&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde has invited policymakers to kick off proceedings earlier in most of the weeks interest-rate decisions are due, according to people familiar with her plans.   
Officials from across the region received an email from Lagarde recently inf...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB May Reach 2% Price Goal Earlier Than Anticipated, Nagel Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440514909&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Euro-area inflation may slow to the European Central Bank’s inflation target earlier than anticipated, according to Bundesbank President Joachim Nagel.
“We assume that we can possibly reach our target rate of 2% earlier than we thought we would in 2025,” the German central banker told...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Shouldn’t Rush Rate Cuts or Plan Too Far Ahead, Vasle Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440514908&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank shouldn’t hurry to lower interest rates or spend too long right now contemplating how far and how quickly they should fall, according to Governing Council member Bostjan Vasle.
Taking policy decisions one step at a time and based on economic data is an approa...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Lagarde Reiterates That Disinflation Is ‘Well on Track’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440507040&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde affirmed that the slowdown in consumer prices is continuing, though she highlighted lingering risks from wage pressures. 
“The incoming information on inflation shows that the disinflation process is well on track,” Lagarde said Friday...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Vujcic Says He’s Open on December Rate Decision</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440498846&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank Governing Council member Boris Vujcic said he hasn’t decided what outcome should be reached at the final interest-rate meeting of the year.
“I’m completely open to any discussion in December,” he told CNBC. “Personally, I don’t know what the decision will be, nor...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro Heads for Longest Weekly Slide Since February on ECB Bets</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440498844&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The euro is on course for its longest weekly slide against the dollar in eight months, pressured by growing expectations that the European Central Bank may deliver a half-point interest-rate cut in December.
The common currency is poised for its fourth straight week of losses, a decli...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Officials Debate If a Half-Point Cut Really Needed: Overview</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440498838&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Views among European Central Bank officials about where to take monetary policy are starting to diverge as the institution’s 2% inflation target moves within close reach.
As policymakers gather in Washington for the International Monetary Fund’s annual meetings, some of the more dovis...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Says Consumer Inflation Expectations Kept Falling Last Month</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440490822&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Inflation expectations of consumers in the euro zone continued declining in September, according to the European Central Bank — giving policymakers further confidence that they may reach their target sooner than previously thought.
Prices are seen rising 2.4% over the next 12 months, ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>