<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>8. Industry</description>
<item>
<title>ECB Wants to Present Results of Strategy Review at Sintra Forum</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428382863&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank wants to present the results of its next monetary-policy strategy review already at next year’s annual forum in Portugal, according to people familiar with the matter.
While the ECB will only likely communicate completion in the second half of 2025 to maintai...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Rehn Says Disinflation, Weak Economy Back September Cut</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428382852&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The slowdown in inflation alongside weakness in the euro-zone economy strengthen arguments to lower borrowing costs next month, according to European Central Bank Governing Council member Olli Rehn.
“The growth outlook in Europe, especially manufacturing, is rather subdued,” the Finni...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Centeno Calls September Rate-Cut Decision ‘Easy’</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428377100&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The decision for the European Central Bank to lower interest rates next month is straight-forward, according to Governing Council member Mario Centeno.
“Of course the most likely move in terms of monetary policy is to continue cutting rates,” the Portuguese central-bank head said Frid...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Gears Up for Next Interest Rate Cut With Inflation Slowing</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428377088&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- European Central Bank officials talking up the prospect of another reduction in interest rates next month will take heart from forecasts suggesting inflation is plummeting back toward their target.
Nine members of the ECB’s rate-setting Governing Council are attending the Federal Rese...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Melrose’s ‘Cash Mountain’ Isn’t Quite That Big, UBS Says</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428371427&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A jet-engine business described by Melrose Industries Plc as a “cash mountain” is actually worth about half the estimate by the UK aerospace engineer’s management, according to analysts at UBS Group AG.
In its Aug. 1 half-year results presentation, London-based Melrose said its risk a...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB’s Vujcic Sees Gradual Interest-Rate Cuts But Urges Caution</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428360799&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The European Central Bank probably has room to slowly lower interest rates as inflation converges toward 2%, but risks remain and officials must proceed carefully, according to Governing Council member Boris Vujcic.
“As long as data fall in line with our projections which foresee infl...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Swiss Minister Rebuffs UBS Lobbying Against More Capital</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428360782&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Swiss Finance Minister Karin Keller-Sutter made clear that the current lobbying campaign by UBS Group AG against new capital requirements isn’t going to sway her. 
“It’s normal that UBS defends its interests, because upcoming legislation will cost them more,” Keller-Sutter told L’Agef...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ECB Says Consumer Inflation Expectations Edged Higher in July</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428355198&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Inflation expectations of consumers in the euro area inched higher, according to the European Central Bank, though the increase is unlikely sufficient to stop officials from pushing ahead with interest-rate cuts.
While prices are seen advancing 2.8% over the next 12 months — the same ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lob fürs Zukunftsfinanzierungsgesetz II</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428382469&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Börsen-Zeitung</author>
<description>Börsen-Zeitung, 24.8.2024
ahe Berlin
Der Entwurf der Bundesregierung für ein Zukunftsfinanzierungsgesetz (ZuFinG) II stößt bei Banken und in der Fondsbranche auf grundsätzliche Zustimmung. Die Deutsche Kreditwirtschaft (DK) bezeichnete das Ziel des Gesetzes, den Finanzstandort Deutschland weiter zu ...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Modern Family</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428371302&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>DER SPIEGEL</author>
<description>Der Begriff »Quality Time« verrät einiges über das heutige Leben. Viele verstehen darunter, im Grunde keine Zeit für die Familie zu haben, aber das halbe Stündchen, das sie doch für Partner und Kinder erübrigen können, effektiv zu nutzen und als ganz tolle Erfahrung zu beschwören. In den USA wurde i...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Verbände wollen für das Bargeld kämpfen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428350508&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>FAZ.NET</author>
<description>Die Deutsche Bundesbank hat mit 27 Verbänden und anderen gesellschaftlichen Organisationen in Deutschland Gespräche über die Zukunft des Bargeldes aufgenommen. Mit dabei waren Gruppierungen vom Zentralverband des Deutschen Bäckerhandwerks über Verbraucherzentralen bis hin zum Deutscher Blinden- und ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>«Kantonalbanken sind transparenter, da sie weniger global verflochten sind als die UBS»</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428346799&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>handelszeitung.ch</author>
<description>Anton Beck
Herr Leuthard, welche Verbindung haben Sie zum Kanton Nidwalden?
Ich bin in Stansstad aufgewachsen. Meine Eltern hatten eine eigene Molkerei und ein Lebensmittelgeschäft. Viele meiner damaligen Kolleginnen und Kollegen sind heute selbständige Unternehmerinnen und Unternehmer und Kundschaf...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Keller-Sutter gibt sich von UBS-Lobbying gegen mehr Kapital unbeeindruckt</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428359166&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>handelszeitung.ch</author>
<description>«Es ist normal, dass die UBS ihre Interessen verteidigt, weil die kommende Gesetzgebung sie mehr kosten wird», sagte Keller-Sutter in einem Interview mit «L'Agefi». Sie bezog sich dabei auf die von der Regierung vorgeschlagenen Regeln, die die Kapitalanforderungen für Banken erheblich erhöhen würden...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ubisoft Entertainment : JP Morgan [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338303&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Ubisoft Entertainment : JP Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient, indirectement par l9intermédiaire des sociétés qu9elle contrôle, 5,04% du capital et 4,63%des droits de vote (23/07/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Edenred : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338302&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Edenred : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse le seuil de 5% du capital et détient 5,005% du capital et 4,94% des droits de vote (30/07/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338296&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Accor : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en baisse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,44% du capital et 4,74% des droits de vote (19/08/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Société Générale : BlackRock, agissant [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338294&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Société Générale : BlackRock, agissant pour le compte de clients et de fonds dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 5,88% du capital et 5,32% des droits de vote (20/08/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrefour : JP Morgan Chase [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338361&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Carrefour : JP Morgan Chase &amp;amp; Co a franchi indirectement en hausse, le seuil de 5% du capital et des droits de vote et détient, indirectement par l9intermédiaire des sociétés qu9elle contrôle, 6,62% du capital et 5,40% des droits de vote (10/07/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Inventiva : UBS Group a [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338359&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Inventiva : UBS Group a franchi en hausse, indirectement, par l9intermédiaire des sociétés qu9elle contrôle, le seuil de 5% du capital et détient, directement et indirectement, 5,10% du capital et 4,08% des droits de vote (22/07/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Verallia : Amundi Asset Management, [...]</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428338300&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Verallia : Amundi Asset Management, agissant pour le compte du FCPE Verallia dont elle assure la gestion, a franchi en hausse, le seuil de 5% des droits de vote et détient 3,38% du capital et 5,31% des droits de vote (22/07/24)....</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>»Fight Club« als romantische Komödie</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428377485&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>SPIEGEL+</author>
<description>Album der Woche:
Fontaines D.C. – »Romance«
Schönheit, das ist eine Binse, liegt ja immer im Auge des Betrachters. Wer sich von der knalligen Farbe und der oberflächlichen Symbolik des großen Luftballonherzchens auf dem Cover des neuen Albums von Fontaines D.C. blenden lässt, übersieht vielleicht da...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lustige Mausikanten</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428361636&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Spiegel.de</author>
<description>Ein Album namens »In einem blauen Mond« fast punktgenau zu veröffentlichen, wenn es tatsächlich das seltene Phänomen des Supermondes am Himmel zu bewundern gibt, das muss man erst einmal hinkriegen. Wenn es nicht geplant war, dann ist es eine glückliche Fügung, so wie auch das unwahrscheinliche Berl...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Soll ich große Summen auf einen Schlag investieren?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2428367837&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>WiWo.de (Wirtschaftswoche)</author>
<description>Erstveröffentlichung: 2024-08-23 12:44:00 letzte Aktualisierung: 2024-08-23 12:44:00
WiWo Coach ist der exklusive Ratgeber-Service für WiWo-Abonnenten. Top-Experten beantworten hier all Ihre Fragen rund um Geldanlage, Vorsorge, Karriere, Steuern und Recht.
Die Frage: Eine Leserin bespart bereits meh...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>