<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Fondos que controlan más del 10% del Sabadell se quedan fuera de la opa</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11773225988014919360</link>
<author>El País</author>
<description>Los productos indexados tienen las manos atadas porque, a causa de su política de inversión, deben ceñirse a su índice bursátil de referencia

Los fondos de inversión que están en el capital del Banco Sabadell son una pieza clave en la opa lanzada por el BBVA. Su aceptación o rechazo de la oferta in...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Global stocks rise as US inflation data hits forecast</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=727718329449660613</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Global stock markets rose on Thursday as US inflation data came in as anticipated, reinforcing the prospect of a Federal Reserve interest rate cut next week.
Meanwhile, the European Central Bank held rates steady for a second consecutive meeting, as expected, and raised its forecasts for eurozone gr...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Global stocks rise as no surprise on US inflation data</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17765760910545156956</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Global stock markets rose on Thursday as US inflation data that came in as expected reinforced expectations of a Federal Reserve interest rate cut next week.
Meanwhile, the European Central Bank held rates steady for a second consecutive meeting, as expected, and raised its forecasts for eurozone gr...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stocks up before US inflation, ECB rate call</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16832397490974792492</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>European and Asian stock markets rose Thursday as traders awaited more US inflation data and the European Central Bank's latest decision on interest rates.
The dollar gained versus the euro and other main rivals.
An update on the US consumer price index is due Thursday, one day after official figure...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>