<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Is the Fed Behind? Bond Traders Bet on Big Rate Cuts Just in Case</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2423380239&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Bond traders who’ve set themselves up for gradual interest-rate cuts starting in September are ramping up side bets in case a sudden slide in the US economy forces the Federal Reserve to be even more aggressive.
As Treasuries advance for a third-straight month, investors are fully pri...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Scholz Is Failing to Engineer a Liftoff for the German Economy</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2423349405&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Germany’s inability to generate meaningful growth is casting a shadow over the long-term prospects for the economy — and political hopes for the three ruling parties under Chancellor Olaf Scholz.
With business confidence last week plummeting and data on Tuesday likely to show that gro...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Infrastruktur fit für die Zukunft machen: Eine Billionen-Aufgabe</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2423373387&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>wallstreet ONLINE</author>
<description>Bekanntlich verändert sich die Welt ständig. Die Veränderungsprozesse sich aus Sicht vieler Menschen in der heutigen Zeit jedoch besonders massiv. Anschauliches Beispiel für die Dynamik der Neugestaltung ist die Infrastruktur – denn während man früher damit in erster Linie Themen wie Straßen, Brücke...</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>