<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Mitsui and Rohto to buy $594 mln Chinese medicines company Eu Yan Sang</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401532642&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>EBR European Business Report</author>
<description>SINGAPORE, April 4 (Reuters) - Japan's Mitsui & Co said on Thursday it had teamed up with Rohto Pharmaceutical Co to buy Eu Yan Sang International in a deal valuing the Singapore-based traditional Chinese medicines firm at S$800 million ($594 million).

Mitsui said in a statement that a special purp...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>AUF- UND ABWÄRTS</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539638&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Euro am Sonntag</author>
<description>Aufwärts
Sergio Ermotti
Bestbezahlter Bankchef
Mit der Übernahme der gestrauchelten Rivalin Credit Suisse ist die Schweizer Großbank UBS zu einem neuen Bankenriesen herangewachsen, der angesichts der damit einhergehenden Klumpenrisiken nicht nur in der kleinen Schweiz großes Unbehagen auslöst. Schwi...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Schonfrist abgelaufen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539647&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Euro am Sonntag</author>
<description>Im Tarifkonflikt bei der Deutsche-Bank-Tochter Postbank haben die Gewerkschaften Verdi und DBV in der Woche nach Ostern zu nahezu flächendeckenden Warnstreiks aufgerufen. Dabei soll es nun auch sogenannte Backoffice-Bereiche treffen, die insbesondere den Service für Kunden abwickeln. Diese Bereiche ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tops und Flops National</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539676&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Euro am Sonntag</author>
<description>Woche vom 27.03. bis 04.04.2024
EVENTIM
Guter Deal
Die Aktie von Eventim hat in der vergangenen Handelswoche rund elf Prozent an Wert zugelegt und einen neuen Höchststand markiert. Ursache für die starke Performance sind Nachrichten rund um eine Übernahme. Konkret will man die Tickettochter des fran...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Italienischer Charme</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539759&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Euro am Sonntag</author>
<description>Als Urlaubsland steht Italien seit jeher hoch in der Gunst nicht nur der Deutschen. Trotz des schlechten Wetters in Norditalien erlebte das Land an Ostern die erste große Touristenwelle des Jahres. Schließlich bietet Italien neben Stränden und attraktiven Landschaften auch schöne Städte, viel Kultur...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>INVESTORS-INFO</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539764&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Euro am Sonntag</author>
<description>AKTIEN
Spendabler Riese
Um knapp 117 Prozent hat die Aktie der Unicredit in den letzten zwölf Monaten zugelegt und damit beispielsweise die Papiere von Deutsche Bank und Commerzbank klar hinter sich gelassen. Auch operativ lief es rund, und davon sollen die Aktionäre profitieren: Der Rekordgewinn vo...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Die Käufer bleiben aus</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401553874&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>IZ aktuell</author>
<description>Offene Fonds und institutionelle Investoren tragen traditionell den deutschen Büroinvestmentmarkt. Jetzt haben sie sich zurückgezogen. Dafür tastet sich Private Equity auf dem Markt vor. Doch die Preise lassen interessierte Käufer abwinken. Keine Immobilien-Assetklasse in Deutschland hat unter dem Ü...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FTSE 100 Live 4 April: Index closes up 0.5%, close to record territory again, US shares plunge late in day</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401541577&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>standard.co.uk</author>
<description>Commodity price strength today helped to underpin the FTSE 100 index during a strong session for mining stocks.

The gains came after Federal Reserve chair Jerome Powell signalled that US interest rates are likely to fall this year.

But after London markets closed, shares on Wall Street plummeted, ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FTSE 100 Live 4 April: Blue-chips higher with record back in sight, Co-op results</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401540079&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>standard.co.uk</author>
<description>Commodity price strength today helped to underpin the FTSE 100 index during a strong session for mining stocks.

The gains came after Federal Reserve chair Jerome Powell signalled that US interest rates are likely to fall this year.

In other developments, shares in Go Compare owner Future and newly...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FTSE 100 Live 4 April: Blue-chips higher with record back in sight, Co-op results</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401540077&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>standard.co.uk</author>
<description>Commodity price strength today helped to underpin the FTSE 100 index during a strong session for mining stocks.

The gains came after Federal Reserve chair Jerome Powell signalled that US interest rates are likely to fall this year.

In other developments, shares in Go Compare owner Future and newly...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FTSE 100 Live 4 April: Blue-chips higher with record back in sight, Co-op results</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401540015&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>standard.co.uk</author>
<description>Future shares surge as it returns to revenue growth



Shares in Country Life publisher Future surged today, as it said its revenue grew again in the first three months of 2024.

The growth was mostly driven by Go Compare, while performance of its magazines has been "resilient". Digital publishing c...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FTSE 100 Live 4 April: Blue-chips slightly higher with record back in sight, Co-op results</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539992&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>standard.co.uk</author>
<description>Ocado chair to exit amid 'time pressure' from NatWest role



Ocado chair Rick Rick Haythornthwaite will leave the boardroom role early next year, as he says he will face more "pressure on my time" as he takes on the same role at NatWest.

Haythornthwaite was picked to replace Sir Howard Davies as c...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FTSE 100 Live 04 April: Co-op Group results; SMMT new car registrations</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401539980&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>standard.co.uk</author>
<description>FTSE 100 seen slightly higher after US rate comments, gold near $2300



Interest rate comments by Federal Reserve chair Jerome Powell failed to alter Wall Street's mood during yesterday's flat session for key US benchmarks.

Powell expects rates will fall at some point this year but that policymake...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Key dates for your finances in 2024</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401566703&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>telegraph.co.uk</author>
<description>Inflation may be easing but it is "too early to call" the end of the cost of living crisis, according to the boss of Tesco.

Impending changes in 2024 will impact your finances, whether you're retired or a young worker on minimum wage. State pension rises, TV licence hikes, expanded childcare suppor...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>US firms offshoring white-collar jobs to UK</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401563443&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>THE TIMES</author>
<description>Lower salaries, tax incentives and a weak pound, alongside the rise of remote working, have led to the United States increasingly offshoring whitecollar jobs to the UK.

Traditionally America has sent manufacturing jobs to China and call centre operations to India, but now big US firms are recruitin...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>