<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Private Equity-Backed Texas Housing Development Taps Muni Market</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436920726&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>Pursuits https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-04/private-equity-backed-texas-housing-development-taps-muni-market (Bloomberg) -- In suburban Texas, a neighborhood complete with an amphitheater, dance hall and goat farm is scheduled to be erected 40 miles from Houston’s downtown — providin...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Short-Dated Muni Bonds Swoon as Fed Rate-Cut Bets Revised</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436902859&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The shortest-dated municipal bonds sold off after a blowout jobs report caused investors to recalibrate the odds of another big interest-rate cut from the Federal Reserve.
On Friday, yields on three-month AAA municipals shot up 29 basis points — the biggest one-day jump since 2022 — a...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Juan Barriobero: “Novo Nordisk, AstraZeneca y ASML son de las pocas firmas europeas con liderazgo global”</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436873469&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Cinco Días</author>
<description>﻿

El gestor español lleva las riendas de uno de los fondos de inversión más emblemáticos del grupo alemán P Administra directamente alrededor de 100 millones de euros

Juan Barriobero de la Pisa (Valencia, 1970) lleva media vida dedicado a los mercados financieros. Tras acabar la carrera de Economí...</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bei Büroimmobilien hält die Krise an</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2436922066&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Handelsblatt</author>
<description>Für die Ladenflächen im Erdgeschoss des Chrysler Buildings gab es lange Zeit nur eine Bezeichnung: „Prime Real Estate“. Das beschreibt eine erstklassige Lage mit einem hohen Interesse von Mietern und Zukunftspotenzial. Der Wolkenkratzer ist mit seiner markanten Spitze schließlich eines der bekanntes...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>