<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>EQS-PVR: Heidelberger Druckmaschinen AG: Release according to Article 40, Section 1 of the WpHG [the German Securities Trading Act] with the objective of Europe-wide distribution</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2572994601220217232</link>
<author>börsenNEWS.de</author>
<description>EQS Voting Rights Announcement: Heidelberger Druckmaschinen AG Heidelberger Druckmaschinen AG: Release according to Article 40, Section 1 of the WpHG [the German Securities Trading Act] with the objective of Europe-wide distribution 08.09.2025 / 11:59 CET/CEST Dissemination of a Voting Rights Announ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Original-Research: LAIQON AG (von NuWays AG): BUY</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5477147733706658670</link>
<author>dpa-AFX Wirtschaftsnachrichten</author>
<description>^ Original-Research: LAIQON AG - from NuWays AG
08.09.2025 / 09:00 CET/CEST Dissemination of a Research, transmitted by EQS News - a service of EQS Group. The issuer is solely responsible for the content of this research. The result of this research does not constitute investment advice or an invita...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Soft H1, but large acquisition to drive earnings: LAIQON's soft H1 results were offset by a significant ...</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5636502435525340808</link>
<author>FN FinanzNachrichten.de</author>
<description>Last week, LAIQON released soft H1 results but issued a new mid-term guidance following a large AuM acquisition. In detail:
Despite 8% yoy higher AuM, reported H1 sales came in muted and declined by 4% yoy to € 14.2m mainly due to the planned phase-out of sold business units (€ -0.4m sales effect).
...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Friedrich Vorwerk Group SE: Release according to Article 40, Section 1 of the WpHG [the German Securities Trading Act] with the objective of Europe-wide distribution</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14964476024699240460</link>
<author>börsenNEWS.de</author>
<description>EQS Voting Rights Announcement: Friedrich Vorwerk Group SE Friedrich Vorwerk Group SE: Release according to Article 40, Section 1 of the WpHG [the German Securities Trading Act] with the objective of Europe-wide distribution 08.09.2025 / 07:05 CET/CEST Dissemination of a Voting Rights Announcement t...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Les gérants crédit abordent la rentrée sous tension</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14908154423907618088</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Le Panel Crédit de LAgefi n'est plus aussi enthousiaste qu'à la veille de la période estivale. Si les fondamentaux et les flux de capitaux demeurent des soutiens solides, les valorisations inquiètent.

Le Panel Crédit de L ' A g e avait abordé la période estivale

plutÎt confiant. La rentrée est pla...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>