<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Fortress, BlackRock Said to Consider Joint Bid for Viridium</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440990849&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- A consortium backed by Fortress Investment Group and BlackRock Inc. is among suitors considering bids for German life insurance consolidator Viridium Group, people with knowledge of the matter said. 
Blackstone Inc., Deutsche Bank AG’s asset management arm DWS Group and Partners Group...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>A 10-Day Test Is Coming for Bond Market Battered by Selloff</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2440976350&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- The US bond market, already stung by the worst selloff in six months, now heads into a crucial two-week stretch that will likely chart its course for the rest of the year. 
A series of market-moving events are coming in rapid succession, kicked off by the Treasury Department’s announc...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Börse Frankfurt-News: "Ein Mehr an Kapitalanlage in der Altersvorsorge wäre gut"</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2441043130&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>dpa-AFX Wirtschaftsnachrichten</author>
<description>FRANKFURT (DEUTSCHE-BOERSE AG) - Fondsmanager Roger Peeters sieht in der Reform der privaten Altersvorsorge eine Chance, die Kapitalmarktbeteiligung zu fördern. Die Einführung einfacher Aktien- und Fondssparpläne könnte insbesondere junge Menschen motivieren, ihre Altersvorsorge aktiv zu gestalten u...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Allianz denkt über die Zukunft der Investmenttochter nach</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2441016503&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>pfefferminzia.de</author>
<description>Beim Versicherungskonzern Allianz überlegt man, wie es mit Allianz Global Investors (AGI) weitergehen soll. Wie die Nachrichtenagentur „Reuters“ meldet, kämen für die Investmenttochter sogar eine Fusion oder ein teilweiser Verkauf infrage. „Reuters“ bezieht sich in seinem Bericht auf vier Personen, ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>