<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Sicherheit durch niedriges KGV: 5 Schnäppchen-Aktien mit Rendite-Turbo</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400419982&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>boerse-online.de</author>
<description>Schnäppchenjäger aufgepasst: Niedrige Bewertungen begrenzen das Abwärtspotenzial und sorgen so für ein hohes Maß an Sicherheit. Für fünf Aktien könnte es dabei besonders gut laufen.
Trotz der Rekordjagd des DAX und der US-Indizes gibt es eine Reihe von Aktien, die so günstig bewertet sind, dass kaum...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>MARKET REPORT: North Sea oil producer Enquest posts loss after hit from windfall tax</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400407650&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>dailymail.co.uk</author>
<description>North Sea oil producer Enquest is to buy back shares from investors for the first time, claiming the windfall tax is hurting the industry.

The energy firm, which was set up in 2010 and operates in the UK and Malaysia, is to launch a £12million repurchase programme this year.

Enquest's finances imp...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>GRAPHIC-Markets brace for more rate cut mood swings after wild Q1</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400408330&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>EBR European Business Report</author>
<description>(Updates prices, latest on Japan's yen, adds comment throughout)

By Naomi Rovnick and Karin Strohecker

LONDON, March 28 (Reuters) - Global bond and equity markets are ending the first quarter on a high, with investors poised for more wild swings after months of lurching between optimism and pessim...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>FACTBOX-European companies cut jobs as economy sputters</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400408265&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>EBR European Business Report</author>
<description>(Updates Stellantis)

March 28 (Reuters) - The highest inflation for decades and the impact of the war in Ukraine have forced companies across Europe into layoffs or hiring freezes.

Here are some cuts announced since December:

AUTOS * BOSCH: the automotive supplier on Jan. 18 said it would cut 1,2...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Les actions réalisent un bon premier trimestre</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400424278&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>L'AGEFI Quotidien (éd. de 7 heures)</author>
<description>Leur

performance sur les trois premiers mois de l'année ne sera pas la raison d'une correction sur les marchés actions.

Après quelques hésitations début janvier, les marchés actions ont repris le rallye débuté n octobre dernier. Ils bouclent le premier trimestre avec des performances à deux chires...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UBS : Sergio Ermotti devient le patron de banque le mieux payé d'Europe</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400424922&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Les Echos</author>
<description>BANQUE

Rappelé aux commandes d'UBS il y a un an, juste après le rachat de Credit Suisse, Sergio Ermotti a perçu en 2023 une rémunération de près de 15 millions d'euros.

La tâche est immense. Et UBS a décidé de rétribuer son patron en conséquence. Nommé il y a un an pour assurer l'intégration de Cr...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Euro 2024 stadiums: Your guide to the 10 venues and host cities</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2400424237&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>telegraph.co.uk</author>
<description>This summer's European Championship will be the first major tournament to introduce gender-neutral toilets at all venues.

The event in Germany will also feature a similar policy for security checks, including body searches, conducted on supporters entering grounds as organisers "embrace gender iden...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>