<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>1. DWS Corporate</description>
<item>
<title>Stabilus SE: Release according to Article 40, Section 1 of the WpHG [the German Securities Trading Act] with the objective of Europe-wide distribution</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=919769981123016818</link>
<author>börsenNEWS.de</author>
<description>EQS Voting Rights Announcement: Stabilus SE
Stabilus SE: Release according to Article 40, Section 1 of the WpHG [the German Securities Trading Act] with the objective of Europe-wide distribution
21.05.2025 / 21:04 CET/CEST
Dissemination of a Voting Rights Announcement transmitted by EQS News - a ser...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Experte warnt: Porsche könnte aus dem Dax fliegen</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5650925872234887899</link>
<author>Backnanger Kreiszeitung</author>
<description>Christian Strenger ist ein Experte für gute Unternehmensführung. Bei Porsche rügt er Verstöße gegen wichtige Regeln.

Stuttgart. Der Finanzexperte Christian Strenger erhebt schwere Vorwürfe gegen die Stuttgarter Porsche AG wegen erheblicher Verstöße gegen die Regeln guter Unternehmensführung. Streng...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bond Market Warns Trump, Congress on Dangers of Swelling Deficit</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9358304430941445140</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- In the world’s biggest bond market, investors are pushing back against President Donald Trump’s tax-cut plan.
On Wednesday, they drove yields on benchmark 30-year Treasuries to as high as 5.1%, leaving them just shy of a two-decade high and sparking declines in stocks and the dollar, ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Korrektur im Aufwärtstrend</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15913250356805138392</link>
<author>Börse Online</author>
<description>► BASIS-DEPOT Deutsche Finanzwerte schwächeln, die beiden französischen Aktien hingegen legen deutlich zu. Unterm Strich steht ein Wochenverlust von 0,49 Prozent

Eine Woche ohne neuen Rekordstand für das Basis-Depot — aber zu verschmerzen. Das Allzeithoch ist trotz des Rückschlags weniger als einen...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>