<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>2. Market Comments & CIO</description>
<item>
<title>Kürt Trump den neuen Fed-Chef zeitnah zur Zinssitzung am Mittwoch?</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=5778770423916908943</link>
<author>Bilanz (Schweiz) online</author>
<description>Bilanz
Mit Spannung blicken die Investoren an den Finanzmärkten derzeit auf die US-Notenbank Federal Reserve. Stärker als der Zinsentscheid am Mittwoch, bei dem die Fed wohl alles beim Alten belassen wird, steht derzeit die Spitzenpersonalie bei der Zentralbank im Fokus: US-Präsident Donald Trump kö...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bond-Market Contrarians Look to Buy US 30-Year Near 5% Yield</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=1512250792577563973</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- In the $30 trillion US Treasury market, some investors see a budding buying opportunity with longer-maturity yields approaching levels rarely seen in the past two decades.
The strategy, from money managers including Columbia Threadneedle Investment and Wellington Management, runs coun...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dollar’s ‘Relentless’ Slide Has Traders Bracing for More Pain</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=8918466091209671332</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Traders in the $9.5 trillion-per-day currency markets are wagering on further losses in the dollar as US policy risks and a resurgent yen drag the world’s primary reserve currency to its weakest level in nearly four years. 
The Bloomberg Dollar Spot Index is logging its steepest four-...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trader setzen Rekordsummen auf den Dollar-Crash</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13027912115956589057</link>
<author>wallstreet ONLINE</author>
<description>Der US-Dollar ist deutlich unter Druck geraten und hat den niedrigsten Stand seit fast vier Jahren erreicht. Der Bloomberg Dollar Spot Index fiel am Dienstag zeitweise um 0,4 Prozent und erlebte bereits die schwächste Woche seit Mai. Auslöser ist vor allem die deutliche Erholung des japanischen Yen,...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>