<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>5. Digital Assets</description>
<item>
<title>PayPal Enables PYUSD Stablecoin for Xoom Cross-Border Money Transfers</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401390275&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- PayPal Holdings Inc.’s Xoom cross-border money transfer service now allows customers to send funds abroad using dollars converted from the PayPal USD stablecoin, the latest sign of crypto’s encroachment on international remittances.
PayPal became the first large financial services com...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ripple Set to Launch US Stablecoin in a Crowded $150 Billion Market</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401378908&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Bloomberg News (English)</author>
<description>(Bloomberg) -- Blockchain developer Ripple Labs Inc. plans to introduce its own dollar-denominated stablecoin, joining a long list of upstarts in a corner of cryptoassets long dominated by Tether Holdings Ltd. 
Ripple’s stablecoin, designed to maintain a constant value of $1, will start trading late...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bitcoin und Ethereum DWS startet eigene Krypto-ETCs</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401412791&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>btc-echo.de</author>
<description></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deka erprobt den digitalen Euro der EZB</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401392319&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung</author>
<description>Der von der Europäischen Zentralbank (EZB) geplante digitale Euro für Privatpersonen stößt in der deutschen Kreditwirtschaft von Großbank bis Sparkasse auf breite Skepsis. Die Geschäftsbanken befürchten die Abwanderung von Spareinlagen zur EZB. Den digitalen Euro für Zahlungen unter Banken, für prog...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>»Die Idee ist King«</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/pmgk2/article_preview.html?id=2401168479&listName=storedesearch</link>
<author>HORIZONT</author>
<description>Marjorieth Sanmartin ist seit 2023 Chief Creative Officer bei Philipp und Keuntje und Fischer-Appelt. Zuvor wirkte die Top-Kreative für Leo Burnett in den USA, BBH und Fallon in London sowie Jung von Matt in Hamburg und TBWA in Düsseldorf. Sanmartin ist Präsidiumsmitglied im ADC und Jurorin bei den ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>