<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>6. Sustainability</description>
<item>
<title>Attraktive Zinsen ohne Tagesgeld oder Festgeld? Die clevere Alternative für Sparer und Anleger</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12078092799396484471</link>
<author>finanzen.net</author>
<description>Die Europäischen Zentralbank hatte die Zinsen im Euroraum seit 2022 zunächst deutlich angehoben und seit 2024 wieder schrittweise gesenkt. Der Einlagensatz, den Banken für ihre Einlagen erhalten, liegt inzwischen bei 2,0 Prozent. Dennoch müssen sich Kunden vieler Banken und Sparkassen mit minimalen ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>LVMH-Aktie: Arnault im Fokus!</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3810872539442953388</link>
<author>finanztrends.de</author>
<description>Die Geduld der Investoren scheint am Ende. Bernard Arnault lenkt LVMH seit fast 40 Jahren, doch eine klare Nachfolgeregelung fehlt weiterhin. Jetzt melden sich erstmals Großaktionäre öffentlich zu Wort und fordern Transparenz. Der 76-Jährige hat die Altersgrenze für seine Doppelrolle als CEO und Cha...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ANALYSIS-Looming Fed rate pause nudges bond investors back into risk</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3768497883132424684</link>
<author>EBR European Business Report</author>
<description>*

Market players expect shallow easing cycle

*

Risk-taking entails extending duration

*

Bond investors still cautious on US credit

*

US rate futures price in less than two Fed cuts in 2026

By Gertrude Chavez-Dreyfuss

NEW YORK, Jan 26 (Reuters) - Bond investors are bracing for an extended pa...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>WOCHENVORSCHAU: Termine bis 9. Februar 2026</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2930002661659664515</link>
<author>dpa-AFX-Line</author>
<description>Wirtschafts- und Finanztermine bis Montag, den 9. Februar 2026



---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
DIENSTAG, DEN 27. JANUAR



TERMINE UNTERNEHMEN
06:00 EUR: Acea, Kfz-Neuzulassungen 12/25
08:00 GBR: Sage Group, Q1-Umsatz
08:00 SWE: Sandvik, Jah...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>HKTDC: The 19th Asian Financial Forum officially kicks off today</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6664013623691644431</link>
<author>FN FinanzNachrichten.de</author>
<description>- Gathering global leaders to examine the economic outlook and reinforce Hong Kong's role as an international financial centre

HONG KONG, Jan 26, 2026 - (ACN Newswire) - The 19th Asian Financial Forum (AFF), co-organised by the Hong Kong SAR Government and the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (H...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Das sind die 11 meistverkauften aktiven Fonds der Maklerpools 2025</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6209542580540782011</link>
<author>dasinvestment.com</author>
<description>Jeden Monat veröffentlichen wir bei DAS INVESTMENT im Zuge einer exklusiven Umfrage die aktiv gemanagten Fonds und ETFs, die die Absatzlisten der deutschen Berater dominieren.
Statt eines Einzelrankings für den Dezember haben wir nun ein Gesamtranking für das Jahr 2025 erstellt. Dafür wurden die Erg...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>EXCLUSIVE-LVMH investors demand clarity on Bernard Arnault succession plan</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13094974845430592894</link>
<author>EBR European Business Report</author>
<description>*

Arnault has five children who all work at the group

*

Age limit for CEO and chair role extended to 85

*

LVMH says it has succession plans, but they won't be revealed

*

Analyst says there's no evidence yet of a 'succession discount'

*

Company to publish annual results on Tuesday

By Tassil...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>ADVISORY dpa NEWS PLANNER for JANUARY 26-FEBRUARY 1, 2026</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=2445278118868458620</link>
<author>dpa-Englisch</author>
<description>All times GMT. If you have any questions about the news schedule or items repeated, please contact the dpa Berlin or Sydney desks at international@dpa.com.
Berlin (Mon-Fri 0700-2200, Sat/Sun 0530-2230) Sydney (Mon-Fri 2130-0730, Sat/Sun 2200-0600)
Sign up here to receive the dpa Weekly News Guide by...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>