<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>Extras</description>
<item>
<title>Verteidigung ist in den Fokus gerückt – das spüren auch Rüstungshersteller</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6167971835636117801</link>
<author>derstandard.at</author>
<description>Ein bis zwei Tage. Solange würden die Munitionsvorräte Deutschlands im Falle eines Krieges ausreichen, warnen Militärexperten. Polen, Bulgarien und Rumänien wiederum sind teilweise noch immer auf Waffen aus der Sowjetzeit angewiesen. Laut der Investmentbank Goldman Sachs hat die Europäische Union (E...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>EQS-PVR: Brockhaus Technologies AG: Veröffentlichung gemäß § 40 Abs. 1 WpHG mit dem Ziel der europaweiten Verbreitung</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15473853018392371921</link>
<author>FN FinanzNachrichten.de</author>
<description>EQS Stimmrechtsmitteilung: Brockhaus Technologies AG Brockhaus Technologies AG: Veröffentlichung gemäß § 40 Abs. 1 WpHG mit dem Ziel der europaweiten Verbreitung 30.12.2025 / 11:01 CET/CESTVeröffentlichung einer Stimmrechtsmitteilung übermittelt durch EQS News - ein Service der EQS Group .Für den In...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>EQS-Stimmrechte: Brockhaus Technologies AG (deutsch)</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3354466242679723237</link>
<author>dpa-AFX-Line</author>
<description>Brockhaus Technologies AG: Veröffentlichung gemäß \u00a7 40 Abs. 1 WpHG mit dem Ziel der europaweiten Verbreitung



EQS Stimmrechtsmitteilung: Brockhaus Technologies AG
Brockhaus Technologies AG: Veröffentlichung gemäß \u00a7 40 Abs. 1 WpHG mit dem
Ziel der europaweiten Verbreitung



30.12.2025 / ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Meat-loving Argentines shun beef as inflation bites</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3000413305795205300</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>As New Year's festivities draw near, meat-loving Argentines are readying their famous "asado" grills -- traditionally laden with steaks, ribs and sausages.
This year, however, menus will feature much more chicken, pork and even vegetables as inflation puts beef beyond the reach of many and societal ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trump, with Netanyahu, says Hamas must disarm</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9893403571481148370</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>US President Donald Trump called again on Hamas to disarm as he began a meeting on Monday with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Nethanyahu, after the Palestinian group's armed wing vowed to keep its weapons.
"There has to be a disarming of Hamas," Trump said as he stood outside his Florida estate wit...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>UN chief says 'get serious' in grim New Year message</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12582493637037251831</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>The United Nations urged global leaders Monday to focus on people and the planet in a New Year's message depicting the world in chaos.
"As we enter the new year, the world stands at a crossroads. Chaos and uncertainty surround us. Division. Violence. Climate breakdown. And systemic violations of int...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trump hints at land strike as Venezuela pressure mounts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18196952372520056021</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>A throwaway remark last week by President Donald Trump has raised questions about whether US forces may have carried their first land strike against drug cartels in Venezuela.
Trump said the US knocked out a "big facility" for producing trafficking boats, as he was discussing his pressure campaign a...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trump has 'positive' call with Putin on Ukraine: White House</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16513183619816202450</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>US President Donald Trump had a "positive" call with Russian counterpart Vladimir Putin on Monday, the White House said, a day after Trump met Ukrainian leader Volodymyr Zelensky in Florida.
"President Trump has concluded a positive call with President Putin concerning Ukraine," Press Secretary Karo...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>US stocks lower to open final trading week of 2025</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7859672698873226626</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Wall Street stocks opened lower Monday as markets entered the final trading stretch of a year in which gains were often driven by artificial intelligence stocks.
Despite periods of worry in recent weeks over AI equity valuations and the robustness of project financing, the Nasdaq has led the major i...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Man accused of fatally stabbing nine in Suriname kills himself</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=3377238135361393421</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>A father suspected of stabbing four of his own children to death in a rampage that claimed nine lives in Suriname's capital killed himself in jail, police said Monday.
The 43-year-old attacker identified only by the initials D.A. hanged himself in a police station cell in the small country on South ...</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>