<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>Extras</description>
<item>
<title>Drones dive into aviation's deepest enigma as MH370 hunt restarts</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7199251956642678286</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Nearly 12 years after Malaysia Airlines flight MH370 vanished with 239 people on board, the search for answers to one of aviation's most haunting riddles resumed Tuesday in the remote southern Indian Ocean.
Armed with cutting-edge deep-sea robots and smarter data, US investigators are scouring the s...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Another police raid on Argentina's football HQ</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18005233893783570951</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Police on Tuesday raided the headquarters of the Argentine Football Association (AFA) in Buenos Aires as part of an investigation into alleged tax evasion by a company associated with it.
It was the latest in a series of raids on Argentine football headquarters and top clubs just months before the w...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Performers cancel concerts at Kennedy center after Trump renaming</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16336235422305344280</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>A prominent jazz group and a dance company have canceled shows at Washington's premier performing arts center to protest its renaming to include US President Donald Trump.
Family members of late president John F. Kennedy and Democratic politicians have already expressed outrage over the change this ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>US unveils sanctions over Iran, Venezuela drones trade</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=14792207166834127411</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>The United States announced sanctions Tuesday targeting Iran's drones trade with Venezuela, a move that comes while Washington ramps up a pressure campaign against Venezuela's leftist President Nicolas Maduro.
The US Treasury Department took aim at 10 individuals and entities based in Venezuela and ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>China fires missiles on second day of military drills around Taiwan</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=7768056504973028697</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>China launched missiles and deployed dozens of fighter aircraft and navy vessels around Taiwan on Tuesday for a second day of live-fire drills aimed at simulating a blockade of the self-ruled island's key ports and assaults on maritime targets.
Taipei, which slammed the two-day war games as "highly ...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>US stocks tick down as tech jitters linger</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=4358362992964273768</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Wall Street's major indexes retreated slightly on Tuesday, as worries over valuations of artificial intelligence stocks lingered in the final days of 2025.
Shortly after trading began, the Dow Jones Industrial Average lost 0.2 percent to 48,380.60 while the broad-based S&P 500 Index edged 0.1 percen...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Unemployment drops to 5.2 percent in Brazil, a new low</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10034627746977607658</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>The unemployment rate in Brazil has reached a new low despite the impact of US tariffs, official data showed Tuesday.
Unemployment for the September to November period was 5.2 percent, the lowest point since 2012 when the Brazilian Institute of Geography and Statistics adopted its current calculatio...</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>