<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>Extras</description>
<item>
<title>Bolsonaro set to return to prison on New Year's Day after surgery</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=6772682181721476716</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Brazil's far-right former president Jair Bolsonaro will return to his prison cell on New Year's Day after spending over a week in hospital following surgery for a groin hernia, his doctors said Wednesday.
Bolsonaro, 70, had surgery on Christmas Day, followed two days later by a procedure to treat re...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trump gets wrong country, wrong bird in windmill rant</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=17725268490493723446</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>US President Donald Trump has blamed wind turbines for killing iconic American bald eagles in a year's end social media post that hit on one of his pet peeves.
There were two problems with this latest lament: the picture in his Truth Social post on Tuesday was taken years ago in Israel, and it's not...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hundreds of tourists evacuated as Machu Picchu trains resume after crash</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12640116953120333405</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Hundreds of tourists were evacuated Wednesday as rail services resumed to and from Peru's Inca citadel of Machu Picchu a day after a head-on collision between two trains killed one person and injured 40.
About 700 Peruvian visitors and 1,300 foreigners of various nationalities had been stranded in t...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trump admin seizes on fraud case to target Somali immigrants</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=15820050476677958928</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>The Trump administration in recent months has latched onto news of a large-scale public benefit fraud scandal to carry out immigration raids and harsher policies targeting Minnesota's large Somali migrant community.
Federal charges have been filed against 98 people accused of embezzlement of public ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trump v 'Obamacare': US health costs set to soar for millions in 2026</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=16480901059040343813</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Iowa farmer Aaron Lehman was already paying a hefty price for health insurance, but his premium is set to skyrocket in January when major government subsidies expire, after US President Donald Trump's Republican party declined to extend them.
That imminent change to the "Obamacare" health insurance ...</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>