<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>PMG</title>
<link>http://beispielwebsite.com</link>
<description>Extras</description>
<item>
<title>Brazil's Bolsonaro heads back to prison after medical treatment</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=10800585323959552355</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Brazil's former president Jair Bolsonaro left a hospital Thursday to return to prison and resume serving a 27-year sentence for plotting a coup.
In a ruling published earlier in the day judges denied a request from Bolsonaro's lawyers to grant him house arrest on health grounds.
Bolsonaro, 70, had b...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New York mayor Mamdani pledges left-wing success after taking office</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=11015461666548574329</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Zohran Mamdani promised Thursday to show left-wing politics can succeed as he took over as New York mayor for a term sure to see him cross swords with US President Donald Trump.
Thousands of people gathered in freezing conditions in the United States' largest city to celebrate the 34-year-old Democr...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Embattled Venezuela releases dozens of jailed dissenters</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=9313562952928348531</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Venezuela Thursday announced the release of 88 people jailed for protesting President Nicolas Maduro's claim to have won July 2024 elections.
Maduro claimed to have won a third six-year term even though the opposition published results it said showed a convincing victory for their candidate. Mass de...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Brazil's Bolsonaro leaves hospital to return to prison</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=13746070939105815379</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Brazil's former president Jair Bolsonaro left the hospital Thursday after a week of treatment and headed back to prison to resume serving a 27-year sentence for plotting a coup.
After the Supreme Court rejected a last-ditch request for house arrest from the former leader, Bolsonaro was seen leaving ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New York mayor Mamdani pledges left-wing success after taking office</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=18257659541857588169</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>Zohran Mamdani promised Thursday to show left-wing politics can succeed as he took over as New York mayor for a term sure to see him cross swords with US President Donald Trump.
Thousands of people gathered in freezing conditions in the United States' largest city to celebrate the 34-year-old Democr...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New York's new mayor says US watching to see if 'left can govern'</title>
<link>https://www.presse-monitor.de/search/read/7000019518?id=12807953426691019041</link>
<author>AFP Englischsprachiger Basisdienst</author>
<description>New York's newly sworn-in mayor, Zohran Mamdani, said the United States will be watching to see whether his leftist brand of politics can succeed.
"There are many who will be watching. They want to know if the left can govern. They want to know if the struggles that afflict them can be solved," he s...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>